Do you think theres a town
in Missouri or someplace
called Sample
And as youre driving into the town
theres a sign and it says
Youre in Sample
MONICA Hey
ALL Hey
RACHEL How did it go with Pete
ROSS Tell us
Youre not gonna believe this
So I go
Im sorry Excuse us
Its a little crowded Do you mind
Could you skooch
TIM
Move over just a little bit
Keep on skooching
Thank you
So guys listen
I go over there and you know Im
TOMAS
Why What is wrong with me
Whats the matter
Tim
I have a feeling
my wife is sleeping
with her gynecologist
How do you know
Hes got access
I know
Its a feeling you get
Like when youre in
somebody elses bowling shoes
Thats the one
So you went to Petes
What happened
TOMAS
Why is this happening to me
Maybe its my wound
Forget it
Its not healed yet
Its oozing
Would you pass the cream
Theres the cream
Thank you very much
Tomas this is gonna be hard
but I wanted it to come from me
What is it
Ive been sleeping with your wife
Youre the gynecologist
Im trying to have
a private conversation
Can I have a napkin
Could you please hand me a napkin
Just give me the thing all right
Enough
And you are no longer my friend
We are finished Nada No more
You are a bastard for doing that
Stay away from me
TIM
Come back
So what were you gonna tell us
I have no idea
What was the big news
Pete wanted to tell you
Or should I say Mrs Monica Becker
Oh keep your name
Dont take his name
He didnt ask me to marry him
ALL Aw
Then definitely dont take his name
He wanted to tell me hes going
to compete in some Ultimate
Fighting Competition thingy
JOEY Pete
RACHEL Why What is it
I dont know exactly
Its sort of like wrestling
Oh
But without the costumes
And its not fake
Its totally brutal
Its two guys in the ring and
the rules are There are no rules
You can bite and pull
peoples hair and stuff
Anything goes except eyegouging
and fishhooking
Whats fishhooking
Whats fishhook
Thanks That would have been
hard to describe
What is that taste
My hands are totally clean
I just gave the duck a bath
DOUG
Thanks for the warm welcome
Its good to have you guys on my team
I come to play I hope you do too
Lets go out there and get them
And remember
There is no I in team
Yes but theres two in martini
So everybody back to my office
You Chuckles Whats your name
Its Bing sir
Im sorry I was just
No no I heard what you said
Funny I like funny
This teams about hard work
but its also about having fun
Good to have you aboard Bing
ROSS
Thats right Ryder
Winona Ryder for six
Thank you
Yeah We have the reservations
RACHEL Yes
All right buddy Way to go
Dude what are you doing
Thank you My boss keeps slapping my
butt and acting like its no big deal
Whatd you do about it
I didnt do anything
I didnt want to be the guy
who has a problem with his boss
slapping his bottom
I gotta tell you I think its okay
to be that guy
Maybe its that jock thing
You know how football players
pat each other after touchdowns
You know I dont understand guys
I mean I would never congratulate
Monica on a great stew
by you know grabbing her boob
I know For a really great stew
youd just
stick your head in between them
Can we please go eat
Yeah what are we getting
Anything but stew
So from now on dont give
your boss a chance to get you
Dont turn your back to him
Or you could teach him
a lesson you know
What you do is rub something that
smells really bad on your butt right
Then when he goes to smack you
his hand will smell
Now what could you rub on your butt
that would smell bad
What if Joey was President
Can I ask you something
Yeah
Okay you can totally say no
but would it be okay with you
if I set Ross up on a date
Oh Uh with who
My friend Bonnie
She always thought Ross was cute
and she asked if I could set it up
But if thats not cool
Which one is Bonnie
You remember her from
my birthday party
Average height
medium build bald
Oh
Thats fine
Great Okay Good for you
All right
You are iron You are steel
Let me ask you how come when I call
your computer support line
I have to wait an hour and a half
Were adding operators all the time
Could we concentrate on my training
Its just hard when I know
I have email I cant get
Hi
Monica
Hi honey
On the table On the table please
Hey um so listen my friends were
telling me a little bit about
this Ultimate Fighting thing
It sounds really dangerous
I dont want you to get hurt
because I kind of like you
I dont want to get hurt either
Im being smart about this
See these guys Theyre
the best trainers in the world
Hoshi was a paid assassin
A housepainter
He used to be a housepainter
Promise me youll be careful
I promise
Are we still on for tonight
Good Because
maybe we could have
a little workout of our own
No No boomboom before big fight
How about just a boom
That was depressing
I just bought a pretzel
from one of the kids from Fame
Ready to go to the movies
Mmhm Oh this is Bonnie
Hi
This is Bonnie
This is Bonnie Youre Bonnie
I can show you an ID if you want
Oh no You look a lot different
than the last time I saw you
Oh yeah Well I just
started wearing bras again
Oh that must be it
Have fun tonight
Thanks You too
You said she was bald
She was bald Shes not now
How could you not tell me
she has hair
I dont know
I hardly ever say that about people
Oh well this is just perfect
Well Im sorry
I thought you said it was okay
I said it was okay when I thought
she was some weird bald chick
That girl has got hair
all over her head
Maybe Ross wont like her personality
Does she have a bad personality
Oh no Bonnies the best
DOUG
Bing
Read your CompuTek proposal
Real home run
Ooh Barely got you that time
Get over here
Come on
Oh yeah Good one
That was a good one
Keep at it team
What is with him
With him
Youre his favorite
Youre his guy
We never get smacked
Thats not true
He smacked you once
Not on purpose
He ricocheted off you and got me
Im telling you
I need some smacks
I got a kid starting Dartmouth
Dartmouth Who went to Dartmouth
Dartmouth sucks
You go to Dartmouth
No sir
There you go Hahaha
ROSS
Hey
God Ross What is that
The Ultimate Fighting Combo
I saved 30 cents
Plus I get to keep the cup Yay
ANNOUNCER
From New York City New York
appearing in his Ultimate
Fighting Championship debut
hes known for his
confrontational business style
Ladies and gentlemen introducing
Pete Becker
I love you Pete
And his opponent
from Huntington Beach California
hes a 300pound
street fighter
Tank Abbott
Boo Boo
Pete Pete
That guys pretty huge
Dont worry
Ill use his strength
and weight against him
Well then that guy is in serious
serious trouble
You go get him Lets go
Here we go gentlemen
Are you ready
Then lets get it on
Uhoh
Hey
Its me
Monica
Can I just tell you how proud
I am of you
It would be nice after hearing
20,000 people chant, "You suck!"
I thought you were nuts at first
but you did it
Now you can just look back at this
with no regrets
Look back
Youre not gonna keep going
Let me ask you a question
Am I the Ultimate Fighting Champion
Well no But
Im not gonna stop until Im
the Ultimate Fighting Champion
That guy stood on your neck
until you passed out
Let me tell you a story
When I set out to create MOSS 865
do you think it happened overnight
No There was MOSS 1
that burned down my dads garage
There was MOSS 2 that would only
schedule appointments in January
And 862 others that I learned from
Just like I learned from this fight
never to let a guy stand on my neck
You didnt know that already
Look Im gonna get better
Okay I promise you
Okay
Just get a lot better
Fast
One other thing
Hoshi thinks you being ringside
may have affected my concentration
Yeah
That was the problem
How long until Petes fight
About five minutes
Theyre interviewing his opponent
Apparently he trains by going to Iran
and pulling the arms off thieves
Wow Ha ha Hot dog
Four please
Im really nervous
Thank you
So how did it go with Bonnie
Oh I gotta tell you
I wasnt expecting to like her at all
I actually wasnt expecting
to like anyone right now
But shes really terrific
Its too bad
No Im saying I liked her
There are other fish in the sea
I think shes great okay
Were going out again
I hear you Are you capable
of talking about anything else
Which ones my turkey burger
The one next to my foot
Sorry
Fights starting
Well be right in
So did your boss try
to slap you again today
Nine times
I had to put on lotion
But itll be okay
Tomorrow I conduct an experiment
And if all goes as planned
my butt will be smackfree
JOEY
Fights over
Excuse me Doug
Hey there sports fan
Bing You got those numbers for me
No I didnt do them
Oh You forgot
No I just didnt do them
Instead I hung out with some
friends and had a couple of beers
So I certainly dont
deserve praise Verbal
or otherwise
I got tanked myself last night
Pretty dicey drive home
Tappan Zee Bridge never looked smaller
Ha ha
Thats okay Youre still
my number one guy Bing
Doug
Hmm
Im a little bit uncomfortable with
the way that you express yourself
Is it the swearing
Is it the constant swearing
Because I gotta tell you if it is
you can just kiss my ass
No Its not about the swearing
Its more about
the way that you occasionally
concentrate your enthusiasm
on my buttocks
Oh
Dont get me wrong
I appreciate the sentiment
Its just that I have a rather
sensitive posterior
And besides its making
all the other guys jealous
Well say no more You know
it takes guts to bring this up
Bing youre okay
Okay
Ha Ah
Ah
Would you rather live in the
shirt pocket of a sweaty giant
or inside his shower drain
Oh my God
Look Its Ross and that girl
Look at that Its a line of ants
Theyre working as a team
Right Oh yeah lt looks
like Ross is breaking up with her
I hope he lets her down easy
Look at that They are not
breaking up Look at them
You know what that is
A second date thats what that is
Look she just put her hand
on his thigh
Thats nothing
Shes very sexually aggressive
Oh God
Its your fault Now he loves her
Hell marry her Its all your fault
You said it was okay
You said she was bald
Was Was was was
We cant let it happen We have to do
something We have to break them up
Just go in there and shave her head
You owe me one bald girl
Okay first of all breathe
Second of all I dont get it
Arent you the one that decided
you didnt want to be with Ross
Yes
Well isnt he your friend
Dont you want him to be happy
Yes
So
Its just you know I didnt
expect him to be this happy so soon
Oh no
What
We killed them all
Its not as bad as it looks
Its a precaution
Im not supposed to move my spine
Please tell me youre stopping now
Im fine Id fight tonight
if theyd let me
Now see this circle
Im marking off here
This is my Zone of Terror
You are insane
Youve got to give this up
I cant until Im
the Ultimate Fighter
I will do it
The day will come when children will
argue over who will win a fight
me or Superman
Not that I could beat Superman
but kids are stupid
Just sit down
Please listen to me
You are terrible at this okay You
are the worst Ultimate Fighter ever
Ever
I have a torn rotator cuff a hairline
fracture in my right forearm
and a severely bruised Adams
apple but that really hurt
Well then you know what
I care about you too much to watch you
hurt yourself like this
So if you have to do this
youll have to do it without me
If youre asking me to quit
then youre asking me
to be someone Im not
Ive got to do this
Then Ive gotta go
Bye
Monica
Yes
Could you leave a note
Im on painkillers
and I might not
remember this tomorrow
So in conclusion the lines
all go up so Im happy
Great job team
Tomorrow at 830
Phil nice job Stevens way to go
Goldberg you maniac
I love you
Bing couldnt have done it without you
Thank you sir
Oh excuse me
I forgot my briefcase you know
by accident
Of course you did Forgot
something else too you bastard
Well what about you
Youre not feeling left out are you
No Heh
No not at all Thats ridiculous
Everybody else got one
and you want one too Dont you
Yes I do
Hahaha
Now get on out of here you
Pete Becker circles the ring
Looks like hes just trying
to feel him out
Bruiser is charging
Run you crazy rich freak
I cant watch this
Check it out Petes winning
Really
No
ANNOUNCER Uhoh Bruiser has Becker on
the canvas and is going for his favorite area
ALL
Oh Oh
Wait If thats his favorite area
why is he being so mean to it
ROSS
This is ironic
Your last boyfriend Richard
didnt want to have kids
And from the looks of it
now Pete cant