That is the most beautiful
engagement ring ever
You should know
you bought like a billion of them
You didnt get one
Tonights the big night
How will you ask her
Itll be perfect
Well go to her favorite restaurant
Ill get her a bottle of the champagne she really
loves therefore knows how expensive it is
Then when the glasses are full instead
of proposing a toast Ill propose
Aw
Sounds perfect
Youll mess up Let me do it
I wont mess up
If she says no
can I have the ring
She wont say no
If
Hey
ROSS Hey
Hey Monica
Give it
Its gone
Phoebe
Hey
Were practically kissing
Anyone free tonight My boss is
hosting a charity event for kids
And the more people I bring
the better I look
So Monica Chandler
We cant go
Were going to dinner Remember
Oh my God Im so sorry
Whats the big deal
I just get mad when Rachel doesnt
remember where were going
Where are you going
How about you guys
Open bar
I think so
I can do that for the kids
Ill come Im making money now
Its time I give some back
You could give back
the money you owe me
Okay Have a benefit
Ross can you come
to a charity event tonight
Oh No I have plans with Elizabeth
Oh Youre already doing
your part for the kids
Its our last night together before she
leaves for camp To be a counselor
I have a question All jokes aside
Where is this relationship going
Wait a minute All jokes aside
I didnt agree to that
Do you see this as longterm thing
I dont know
You are 1 2 years older than her
Wait a minute
Does everyone feel this way
Yeah
Yeah sort of
Uh wow Uh I thought
you were making jokes I had no idea
You guys are wrong Yes there is
a chronological age difference
But I never notice it
because she is very mature
It doesnt matter what you guys think
Im dating Elizabeth not you
Not what she said last night
See now he could date her
Will you marry me
Hey you marry me
Whats going on little elves
Its the big night
We wanted to wish you luck
Yeah Have the ring
In my pocket
Oh
Pheebs
Oh Ha ha
Will you guys get out of here I want this
to be a surprise and shes gonna know
Yeah guys Get out of here
Hey Hi guys
You look beautiful
Aww Thank you
Whats going on
Were just really
excited about this charity event
that we have to go to
Here
Thank you
So whats going on here
Well uh this is a silent auction
They lay the stuff here
You write down your offer
The highest bid gets it
No I know what a silent auction is
Whats going on with your hair
Uh why
No its nice
Nice to see you
So glad you brought someone
Someone I brought people
This is Phoebe
Phoebe this is Mr Thompson
Hes the head of my department
Oh hi
And I also brought my friend Joey
Ohh Shrimp toast
You know I dont know where he is
I hope youre gonna bid
Actually I was about to bid
on this lovely trip to Paris
Nice choice
Yeah
Good luck
Thank you
Ha
Okay 2000
Shut the door Shut the door
Whats going on
Guys across the hall
are throwing water balloons
Call the police Thats what I did
to kids in my building
No its a water balloon fight
We started it
Oh Hmm
Um I just stopped by to see
if you wanted to see this play tonight
Um its excellent The director is
Who drank all the kamikazes
Nobody We put them in here
You want some
No I Okay okay
Could I talk to you for a second
Yeah sure
Um so this play um
what do you think
Its gotten great reviews
Attack
Put your balloons down
You put your balloons down
Now this is a nice suit
Our next item is
the romantic trip to Paris
It goes to Emil Alexander
with a high bid of 2300
Oh So close
Hey you guys look
Got me some drinks
What are you doing
Open bar
THOMPSON Finally our biggest item
of the night
The 22foot
Gentlemans Daysailer sailboat
The winning bid
was a whopping 20000
I won
That was my guess
What What What
I guessed 20000
Joey it is an auction
You dont guess You buy
What
I dont have 20000
Congratulations on your new boat
Joey Tribbiani
Joey sit down
Forget her You enjoy this Whoo
What are you doing
One nation
under God indivisible
with liberty and justice for all
Ha ha I remembered it
The champagne is here
Are you okay
Yes Yes
Im good Are you good
Are you perfect
Yeah Im okay
Im a little cold
Can I have your jacket
Oh Yeah
Uh no you cant have my jacket
Because then I would be cold
If you thought youd be cold
you should have brought a jacket
Uh other than that are you okay
Are you sure youre okay
Yes Im fine
In fact Ive been fine
for a long time now and I think
the reason is you
Thats sweet
Okay Um
Before I met you
I had really little life
And I couldnt imagine growing old
Oh my God
I know But let me say it
Oh my God Richard
What Im Chandler
Oh thats Richard
Maybe he wont see us
Richard
Monica Chandler
CHANDLER Hey
I dont know why I did that
Its good to see you
You too You let your hair grow
Yeah Oh thats right
you always wanted me to
I see your mustache is back
Well my nose got lonely
And you dont have a mustache
which is good Ha ha
Im Chandler
I make jokes when Im uncomfortable
Im sorry Lisa Monica Chandler
We used to date
Richard
No ones supposed to know about us
See I did it again
Chandler sit down
Ill sit down
MONICA
Good to see you
Your table is ready sir
Oh Good to see you guys
Yes
If you prefer this tables available
That might be fun
What were you thinking
I didnt know it was an auction
I figured Id take a guess
Help a charity Free boat
Why would a charity
give away a free boat
I dont know Charity
Oh
Well just buy the damn boat
Phoebe dont you think
youve had enough to drink
Im just helping the kids
How is you drinking helping the kids
Because the more I drink the less
there is for the kids to drink
Mr Tribbiani
Your contribution brings us
a big step closer
to building the youth center
Just out of curiosity
how much is that boat worth
I think it was valued at 1 9000
Hey I was pretty close
Uh so bad news
Um I cant buy the boat
I dont have any money
Joey Joey good one
Good Very good
So uh I think Im gonna take off now
You cant leave Joey
You agreed to buy that boat
It is a contract
Plus if you leave
my boss is gonna kill me
Well what am I gonna do Rach
I dont have that kind of money
I know Okay okay okay okay
This is what well do
Well go to the next highest bidder
and well let them buy it
Then youre just gonna
pay the difference
Okay
I dont know why the kids need a
youth center anyway
They should just watch TV after school
like I did And I turned out fine
Not great
So were hiding in the bathroom
Then I sneak out But before
Monica can her parents come in
I hid in the shower
next thing you know
theyre going at it on the floor
Oh my God
I got a good one
I once walked in on both my parents
making love to the same guy
Its so great seeing you guys again
Id like to make a toast
Uh as a poet once said
ln the sweetness of friendship
let there be laughter
and sharing of pleasures
for in the dew of little things
the heart finds its morning and is
refreshed
Aw
What
Oh my God You guys
Before you say anything have we got a story
for you Guess who we bumped into
Who
Richard
Oh Oh
I thought you were going out
with Elizabeth
I was Uh she was a little busy
with a water balloon fight
Sometimes grownups have commitments
they cant get out of
Maybe she is too young for me
When I was over there
I felt like I was a babysitter
I finally see what you were talking
about I dont know what to do
Just weigh the good stuff about
the relationship against the bad
Thats what I did when I first started
weighing stuff
Okay um bad stuff
Im 1 2 years older than she is
If school finds out youre fired
Shes leaving for three months
For camp
Okay good stuff Um
Well shes sweet and pretty and
The only question you need to ask
is do you see a future
Do you see yourself marrying her
My God You did it already
You married her didnt you
No I didnt do that
Its just
Honestly no
I dont see a big future with her
Okay I think thats your answer
I gotta talk to her
I hate this part
Forget Elizabeth
If youre not careful
you may not get married
at all this year
Rach Rach
Next highest bidder is at table one
Great
The guy who got the Paris trip
is at table four
You care about the guy
who won the Paris trip
Its a trip for two
Excuse me
Excuse me ls the person who won
the Paris trip at this table
That was me
Oh Enchanté
Uh is there
a Mr Bowmont at this table
Thats me
Ah
Hello This is your
lucky day Mr Bowmont
The uh Gentleman Daysailer
has become available again
I believe you made a bid of 1 8000
You have to pay that
Its not just a guess
I was actually relieved
uh I didnt win the boat
My wife wouldve killed me
Are you kidding
Shell love this boat
What is your wifes name
Its Pam
Its Pam Just imagine this
The Pam
Aw
I dont think shed like that
Okay Uh imagine this
The Mr Bowmont
Ooh
I dont think so
Okay look Let me paint you
a little picture All right
You are setting sail up the Hudson
Youve got the wind in your ha Arms
You get all that peace and quiet
youve always wanted
You get back to nature
You can go fishing
You get one of those hats
people call you captain
And then when youre old Cappy
What the hell Its for a good cause
All right
No way Its mine
What
The stuff you said I want that
But Joey you dont have 20000
Who cares Ill make payments
I want the Mr Bowmont
Oh my God Youre back
Let me see your hand
Why do you want to see my hand
I want to see whats in your hand
the trash
Ew its all dirty
You should throw this out
Okay
What did you just do
What happened
Richard was there I couldnt do it
Oh no
I was gonna do it tomorrow and surprise her
Now youve ruined it
We didnt
Who walks into a room
and asks to see a persons hands
A palm reader a manicurist
a hand doctor
Glove salesman
Good one
This is terrible
What am I gonna do
She only suspects something
So just throw her off the track
Ill make her think uh marriage
is the last thing on my mind
Yeah Convince her youre scared
of commitment
I can do that
Ive had 30 years of practice
Being you is finally gonna pay off
Had to go to the basement
some idiot keeps stuffing
the chute with pizza boxes
That guys still doing that
Hey My God let me see your hand
No youre too late
She already took out the trash
ROSS Wow I have never had
such a healthy breakup
She was such a grownup about it
She didnt seem too immature for me
Did I just make a huge mistake
Ross Wait
Elizabeth thank God
I was just thinking about
You suck
What
Okay
Breakups still on
Here she comes
Do I look like a guy
who doesnt want to get married
Yeah
And also a little like a
French guy
I never noticed that before
Hey guys
JOEY Hey
What are you up to
Just hanging out
Talking about uh web sites
Ha
Ahem We saw this interesting website
about marriage
How unnecessary it is
How its a way for governments
to keep tabs on you
Yeah Big Brother Ha ha
Thats a little crazy
Although I am glad youre looking
at other things on the Internet
Got me thinking why would anybody
want to get married
Why To celebrate the relationship
To solidify the commitment
To declare your love for one another
to the world
Eh
Okay Well thats good to know
The Mr Bowmonts here
A customer wants to compliment you
Shall I let him in
Sure I love this part
Come on in
Hi
Richard
Im not here to compliment the chef
Oh I hate when people come back
to compliment the chef
Like Ive nothing better to do
Whats up
It was great seeing you
the other night
Good to see you too
Come down here
to tell me that
No Came here to tell you
something else
Came here to tell you
I still love you