Oh thats good
Okay All right Phoebe
Okay okay
If I were omnipotent for a day
I would want um world peace
no more hunger
good things for the rain forest
And bigger boobs
Well see you took mine so
Chandler what about you
If I were omnipotent for a day
Id make myself omnipotent forever
Heh See theres always one guy
If I had a wish
Id wish for three more wishes
Hey Joey
Hey buddy
What would you do
if you were omnipotent
Probably kill myself
Excuse me
Hey if Little Joeys dead
then I got no reason to live you know
Joey uh omnipotent
You are
Ross Im
How does she do that
I cannot sleep in a public place
Would you look at her
Shes so peaceful
Yeah
What What Hi
Its okay you know
You just nodded off again
Oh
Whats going on with you
I got no sleep last night
Why
My grandmother
has this new boyfriend
and theyre both kind of insecure
in bed so
And deaf
So theyre constantly having to reassure
each other that theyre having a good time
You have no idea how loud they are
You can stay with Rachel and me tonight
Thanks
Ninetyfive 96 97
See I told you
Less than 100 steps from our place to here
You got way too much free time man
Hey theres the birthday boy
Ross check it out Hockey tickets
RangersPenguins tonight at the Garden
Were taking you
Happy birthday pal
We love you man
Its funny
my birthday was seven months ago
So
So Im guessing you had an extra ticket
and couldnt decide
which one of you got to bring a date Huh
Well arent we
Mr TheGlassisHalfEmpty
Oh my God Oh
Is today the 20th October 20th
I was hoping you wouldnt remember
Oh
Whats wrong with the 20th
Eleven days before Halloween
All the good costumes are gone
Todays the day Carol and I
first consummated
our physical relationship
We had sex
You know what
I better pass on the game
I think Im just gonna go home and think
about my exwife and her lesbian lover
The hell with hockey Lets all do that
Come on Ross You me Joey ice
Guys night out
Come on what do you say big guy
Huh Huh Huh
What are you doing
I have no idea
Come on Ross
All right all right
Maybe it will take my mind off it
You promise to buy me a big foam finger
You got it
All right
Look look look My first paycheck
Look at the window
Theres my name Hi me
I remember the day
I got my first paycheck
There was a cavein in one of the mines
and eight people were killed
Wow you worked in a mine
No I worked at a Dairy Queen Why
God isnt this exciting I earned this
I wiped tables for it I steamed milk for it
And it was totally
not worth it
Whos FICA
Whys he getting all my money
I mean what Chandler look at that
Oh this is not that bad
Oh youre fine yeah for a first job
You can totally totally live on this
Oh yeah yeah
By the way great service today
Ooh
Oh yeah
Terrific
It was excellent
Unbelievable
And all that milk and stuff Great
Hockey
Hockey Hockey
Hockey Hockey Hockey
Rachel
Oh my God
I swear Ive seen birds do this
on Wild Kingdom
What are you guys doing here
Well we were in the city shopping
and your mom said you work here
and its true
Yeah
Look at you in the apron
You look like youre in a play
God look at you You are so big
I cant believe it
I know I know Im a duplex
So whats going on with you
Well guess who my dads making partner
in his firm
And while were on the subject
of news
Look look I have elbows
Passes it up to Leetch
Leetch spots Messier in the crease
Heres the pass
Oh Oh
Well take a timeout while Messier stops
to look at some womens shoes
Carol was wearing boots just like those
the night that we first
you know
In fact she uh
She never took them off Ha ha
Its because we Sorry Sorry
I cant believe
What
Peach pit
Yes bunny
That night we uh had
Peaches
Actually nectarines but basically
Couldve been a peach
Then we uh
Then we got dressed
and I walked her to
the bus stop
Im fine
Hey that womans got an ass
like Carols
What
I thought we were trying to find stuff
Oh come on you guys
Tell me all the dirt
Well the biggest news
is still you dumping Barry at the altar
All right lets talk reality for a second
Okay
When are you coming home
What
Guys Im not
Heh Come on This is us
Im not
This is what Im doing now
Ive got this job
Waitressing
Heh Im not just waitressing
I mean Im
I um
I write the specials
on the specials board
And I take the dead flowers
out of the vase
Um oh and sometimes Arturo lets me put
the little chocolate blobbies on the cookies
Well your mom didnt tell us
about the blobbies
Hey Rach How was it with your friends
Okay how would you like
some Tiki Death Punch
Whats that
Well its rum and
Okay
We thought since Phoebes staying over
wed have a slumber party
We got some trashy magazines
we got cookie dough we got Twister
Ooh ooh And I brought Operation
But I lost the tweezers
so we cant operate
But we can prep the guy
Rach its the Visacard people
Oh God Ask them what they want
Could you please tell me
what this is in reference to
Yes hold on
Um they say theres been unusual activity
on your account
But I havent used my card in weeks
That is the unusual activity
They just wanna see if youre okay
They wanna know if Im okay
Okay they wanna know if Im okay
Okay lets see
Well lets see
The FICA guys took all my money
Everyone I know is either getting married
or getting pregnant or getting promoted
and Im getting coffee
And its not even for me
So if that sounds like Im okay okay
then you can tell them Im okay Okay
Uh Rachel has left the building
Can you call back
All right Come on
Lets play Twister
Sorry
Sorry sorry sorry
Uhoh
What There was ice there
that night with Carol
Plastic seats
Four thousand angry Pittsburgh fans
No actually I was just saying
it looks like were not sitting together
But now that you mention it
there was ice there that night
It was the first frost
We were
Sit Just sit down Sit
You should feel great
Youre doing this amazing
independent thing
Monica what is so amazing
I gave up like everything And for what
You are just like Jack
Jack from downstairs
No Jack and the Beanstalk
Ah the other Jack
Yeah right
See he gave up something
but then he got those magic beans
And then he woke up
and there was this big plant
outside of his window
full of possibilities and stuff
And he lived in a village
and you live in the Village
Okay but Pheebs Pheebs
Jack gave up a cow
I gave up an orthodontist
Okay I know I didnt love him but
Oh see Jack did love the cow
But see it was a plan you know
It was clear
Everything was figured out
and now everythings just kind of like
Flupie
Yeah
Youre not the only one
We dont know where were going
You gotta figure at some point
its gonna come together
and its just gonna be unflupie
Yeah like thats a word
Okay but Monica
what if it doesnt come together
Pheebs
Well because you just
I dont like this question
Okay see See you guys
What if we dont get magic beans
I mean what if all weve got are
beans
Get him Get him Get him
Get Yes
Youre not laughing now are you pal
Thats all you need a bunch of toothless
guys hitting each other with sticks
Pass it Pass it
Hes open hes open
Shoot it shoot it shoot it
Whoa Oh
Whoa
Hey look were on that TV thing
Ooh ooh ooh
I got it
Hey hey we got it Hey
Excuse me
It says to call this number if youre not
completely satisfied with this candy bar
Well Im not completely satisfied
Listen its kind of an emergency
I guess youd know that
or wed be in the predicament room
Hold on Fill these out Sit over there
Look I dont wanna
make any trouble okay
But Im in a lot of pain here all right
My face is dented
Well youll have to wait your turn
Well how long do you think itll be
Any minute now
Hey listen Ooh
I wake up and I start to cry
Aint no hope in
Oh Im so sorry you guys
I didnt mean to bring you down
No you were right
I dont have a plan
Pizza guy
Thank God
Food
Phoebe
What
Do you have a plan
I dont even have a pla
Hi One mushroom
green pepper and onion
No no no Thats not what we ordered
We ordered a fatfree crust
with extra cheese
Wait youre not G Stephanopoulos
No
Oh man My dads gonna kill me
Wait
Did you say G Stephanopoulos
Yeah this one goes across the street
I must have given him yours
Oh bonehead Bonehead
Wait was this a small Mediterranean guy
with curiously intelligent good looks
Yeah that sounds about right
Was he wearing a stunning blue suit
And a power tie
No pretty much just a towel
Oh God
Oh Oh
Oh my God
You want me to take this back
What Are you nuts
Weve got George Stephanopoulos pizza
Here
Uh Pheebs
Yeah
Whos George Snuffleupagus
Thats Big Birds friend
I see pizza
Oh I wanna see Let me see Let me see
Hello Who are we spying on
You know the White House adviser
Clintons campaign guy
The one with the great hair
sexy smile really cute butt
Oh him The little guy Oh I love him
Ooh Oh wait Wait I see a woman
Tell me its his mother
Definitely not his mother
Oh no
Oh wait shes walking across the floor
Shes walking shes walking
Shes going for the pizza
Hey thats not for you bitch
Dr Max to Center 456
Excuse me
Weve been here for over an hour
and people less sick than my friend
have gone in
I mean that guy with the toe thing
Whos he sleeping with
Oh come on Dora Dont be mad
I know we both said some things
we didnt mean
but that doesnt mean
we still dont love each other
You know I feel like Ive lost her
Lights still out
Yeah
Well maybe theyre napping
Heh Please Theyre having sex
Shut up
So what do you think George is like
I think hes shy
Oh yeah
Yeah I think you have to draw him out
And then when you do
hes a preppy animal
Come on
I remember the moonlight coming in
through the open window
and her face
had the most incredible glow
Yes the moon the glow
the magical feeling
You did this part
Could I get some painkillers over here
please
Hes right enough already
What is the big deal about today
So you slept with her for the first time
So what
You slept with her
for seven years after that
Its just a little more complicated
than that
What What is it That she left you
That she likes women
That she left you for a woman
that likes women
A little louder
Theres a man on the 12th floor in a coma
who didnt quite hear you
Then what
My first time with Carol was
Was my
What
It was my first
time
With Carol
Oh
So in your whole life
youve only been with one
Oh
Oh boy Hockey was a big mistake
Theres a whole bunch of stuff
we couldve done tonight
Okay Okay I got one
Do you remember that vegetarian pâté
that I made that you loved so much
Uhhuh
Well unless goose is a vegetable
Oh Oh
Hahaha
Okay fine fine
Now I dont feel so bad
about sleeping with Jason Hurley
What You slept with Jason
You had already broken up
How long
Just a couple hours
Oh thats nice
Okay okay okay I got one
Anyway
The valentine Tommy Rollerson left
in your locker was really from me
Excuse me
Oh hello
Like he was really gonna send you one
She was a big girl
Really
Well at least big girls dont pee
in their pants in seventh grade
I was laughing You made me laugh
Oh my God
There he is There he is There he is
Where
Right where weve been looking all night
Oh hes so cute
Oh George baby drop the towel
Come on drop the towel
Drop the towel
Please drop the towel Drop it
Wow
Man can you believe hes only had sex
with one woman
I think its great
You know its sweet Its romantic
Really
No are you kidding
The guys a freak I judge him
Hey man
Hey buddy
Ah Ah
Oh
Thats attractive
Oh I thought you were great
in Silence of the Lambs
Oh come on admit it
all things considered you had fun tonight
Fun Where was the fun
Tell me specifically
which part was the fun part
Wheres my puck
Oh The kid has it
The kid
Ahem Excuse me uh thats my puck
I found it
Finders keepers losers weepers
You gotta do it man
Oh yeah Well Im rubber youre glue
Whatever you
I cant do it
Listen uh give me back my puck
No
Yes how about
No come here Just give me my puck
No no no
Hey no roughhousing in my ER
Give me my puck Unh
Now that was fun
Okay Monica
Right foot red
Couldve played Monopoly but no
Thanks
Okay Pheebs Right hand blue
Good
Hmm
Hello
Oh Rachel its the Visacard people
Oh okay Will you take my place
All right Yes this is Rachel
No
Oh
Hello
Oh yeah No I know
I havent been using it much
Oh well thanks but Im okay really
To the green to the green
Oh no
To the green
Ive got magic beans
No no never mind
To the left To the left
Im fine