Hey whats going on
I found a note on my door
Come to Monicas
Bring champagne
and a Three Musketeers bar
Yeah Ill take that
Whats up
Monica and I are engaged
Oh my God
Congratulations Where is she
Im engaged Im engaged
Shes been there for 20 minutes
You didnt hear
I thought it was a kid yelling Im gay
Can I bring her in
Let her stay Its sweet
Im getting married Im gonna be a bride
MAN
Shut up
No I will not shut up because Im engaged
Oh big talk Why dont you
come here and say that to me
My fiancé will kick your ass
Come on apartment 20 apartment 20
You get her in you bolt the door
Ill be in the closet
Okay wait wait wait Okay shh
Okay Um
I just want to say that I love
you guys so so much
and thank you for being here
on my special night
Our special night
It just wouldnt be my night Our night
if you werent here to celebrate
with me Us Damn it
Its okay I want this to be your night too
To Monica
Come on wait stop it
Okay to Monica
GROUP To Monica
Have you decided on a band for the
wedding because Im kind of musical
She got engaged a few hours ago
I doubt shes had time to think
Speaking of chiming in
remember burning my apartment
Yeah youre on your own
We should get dressed up
and go have champagne at the Plaza
Oh okay
GROUP Yeah
I cant stay too long
I gotta get up early for an audition
I gotta look good
Im supposed to be playing a 1 9yearold
What
So when you said get up early
did you mean 1 986
You guys dont think I look 1 9
Oh 1 9 We thought you said 90
GROUP
Oh
Okay everybody lets go
Okay
Is my candy bar around here
No you ate it all
I was afraid of that
You know what shoes would look great
with this ring
Diamond shoes
Youre not getting dressed
Know what I mean
Yeah but I dont think we have time
Theres gonna be a wedding
Youre gonna be the bride
Two hundred people are gonna be
looking at you in a clean white dress
Lets do it
Chandler it happens to lots of guys
Youre tired you had a lot of champagne
Dont worry about it
Im not worried Im fascinated
You know Its like biology
Which is funny because in high school
I failed biology
and tonight biology failed me
Check it out I could play this
while the guests are coming in okay
I thought he was gay
But here I am singing
On his wedding day
Phoebe no
If youd let me finish it goes on
to say that hes probably not gay
You guys dont have this problem
youre made of wood
Hey you look great
Hey
Oh thanks
You okay over there
I dont know You know I feel a little
You know what Never mind Ill be fine
Dont worry about it Youre probably tired
you had a lot of champagne
It happens to everybody
Hey Wow
Hi
Happy Monicas Night
Well thank you You too
Can you believe
they are actually getting married
Well sure but I get married all the time
You okay
Yeah I guess
Do you think well ever have that
You mean we you and me
Oh no no no
We you with someone me with someone
Good you scared me a minute
I know Shake it off
Its just because you and I
we were like a nightmare
No but there were some good times
Absolutely Like there was
Surely you can think of something
Just give me a minute
Oh well yes
I can think of one good thing
What
You were always good at the
at the uh the stuff
Yeah I
I was good at the stuff
Mmhm Yup
I really liked your hands
My hands
Yeah
Uhhuh
Way to go guys
You were really good at the stuff too
Oh I know
Hey you know what we never did
Oh no not that
We never had bonus night
A what
You know bonus night
Two people break up
but they get back together for one night
One night just sex
No strings attached
Yeah yeah we never had that
No
Okay this is getting a little crazy
Um I mean
Im sure it would be amazing
but I really dont think
it would be a good idea
I really
really
dont
Whats up
Whats up dude
Take whatever you want
just dont hurt me
You playing a little PlayStation huh
Thats wack
PlayStation is wack
Whats up with the wack PlayStation
whats up
Huh
Come on am I 1 9 or what
Yes on a scale of one to 1 0
1 0 being the dumbest a person can look...
you are definitely 1 9
Come on really How old
Young Youre a manchild okay
Now get changed everybodys ready
And please please keep my underwear
Oh thanks
Okay
Joe
Yeah
Uh
Youve had a lot of sex right
When today
Some not a lot
The reason Im asking
is because I had kind of a uh
I was unable to
I really wanted to but I couldnt
There ha hm
There was an incident
Dont worry about that man That happens
Its happened to you
Yeah once
Well whatd you do
I did it anyway
Phoebe come on lets go
Come on
Why arent you dressed yet
I wrote the best song for your wedding
Check this out
Phoeb
If you get ready now you can play
Really
Yes
Thats so exciting Thanks Mon
But if you touch my guitar again
Ill have to pound on you a little bit
Fair enough Get ready Ill get everybody
Finally we can start celebrating my
Im sorry apparently I opened
the door to the past
Okay Monica Mon
Okay what you just saw
Can I ask you just a little question
Why tonight
What
I waited my whole life to be engaged
And unlike some
I only plan on doing this once
Maybe its selfish Im sorry but I hoped
tonight could just be about that
Oh honey but it is
No its not
Now its about you getting back together
See you kind of stole my thunder
We did not steal your thunder
We are not getting back together
Yeah no and nobody even saw
Yeah
Thats true
We just kissed
ROSS lt was just a kiss
You guys kissed
What does this mean
Are you back together
Can I sing at your wedding
Thunder being stolen
Phoebe its nothing
Lets not make a big deal of this
ROSS lt was a onetime thing
It doesnt even matter
Oh my God
I cannot believe you guys
are talking about this
Problems in the bedroom
are between a man and woman
All right Now Chandler
is doing the best he can
I dont think thats
what they were talking about
What a great night
Chandler cant do it they kissed
What
You guys kissed This is huge
No its not huge
People thinking its huge
has led Monica to believe
were stealing her thunder
which we arent
Were still talking about it
That and Chandlers problem
Monica listen listen
Would you feel better if we stopped
talking about Ross and Rachel
That would be lovely
You got it
Now I can pass for 1 9 right
Yes you can pass for 1 9
Really
Yes
Seriously
Seriously no Okay You can play
your own age which is 31
Im 30
Joey you are not Youre 31
Oh crap
So the Plaza Well get some mai tais
Maybe no more for you though
You know I think I dont feel like
going to the Plaza
GROUP Why
RACHEL This is ridiculous
I dont want to talk about it
I dont Especially with you
Pssh That is wack
Yeah
Ill play it at the wedding
Yeah well well see if they
actually let you play huh
They tell you anything you want to hear
like You look 1 9
Then they just take it away
like No you dont
Monica wont take this away
Wouldnt she
Would she
You ate my candy bar
ROSS
Guess who
Hey
Hey I just realized we kind of left
some stuff up in the air
What did Monica mean
I dont want to talk
especially with me
Why not especially you and me
We were both kissing
Still thinking about it
Im serious What did she mean by that
Especially you
Oh who cares
I care
And so do I
I have to talk to her
Will you let me get changed
Okay sure
Am I going to let you watch me
No
I cant believe her Its just so typical
I know youre upset but dont forget
there is going to be a wedding
You are going to throw the bouquet
and then a honeymoon
Maybe in Paris
Paris
We will take a moonlit walk
on the Rue de la blahblahblah
Keep talking
We will sprinkle rose petals
on the bed and make love
not just because its romantic
but because I can
I love you
CHANDLER
Mmm
Bonjour monsieur
Dont say anything
you might scare it away
Its Paris Who knows were here
Hi Pheebs Whats up
You said I could sing at your wedding
so I need a small deposit
What
Goodfaith money to hold the date
Were not giving you a deposit
for our wedding
Oh I see
They break your heart dont they
You know I dont really need
their permission
You want to sing at their wedding
sing at their wedding
Yeah and if you want to look 1 9 then you
You got to do something about your eyes
Whats wrong with my eyes
They give you away
Theres too much wisdom in there
Put some tea bags on them for 1 5 minutes
Thatll get rid of my wisdom
Maybe 1 0 minutes for you
Give her the deposit
give her the ring I dont care
Yes
What did you mean when you said
you didnt want to talk to anyone
especially me
What a great apology
And you accept it Byebye
No seriously what was
the especially me part about
Lets just say its not the first time
youve stolen my thunder
Wha
Hey heres a thought
Monica what are you talking about
My sweet 1 6 You went to third base
with my cousin Charlie
Ah third base
It was all everybody could talk about
The only reason I did that
was because your party was so boring
We had a caricaturist
Oh
Guess who wont be asked to sing
Somebody named Geller
And somebody else named Bing
Monica your sweet 1 6
was like a million years ago
Yet here you are doing it again
Oh I dont want to steal your stupid thunder
Why else would you have
made out with Ross
Got me
Easy mimey the moment has passed
It aint gonna happen
Itd be nice if I could have this night
I never wanted any part of your night
No one was supposed to see us
Is that why you did it in the secret hallway
where nobody ever goes
Uh Rachel Ive been thinking
I dont think us getting together
tonight is such a good idea
Im calling it off
Way to save your dignity my man
Mon why why would I ever want
to take away from your night
I dont know maybe you feel
a little resentful
Maybe you thought youd get married first
Maybe you cant stand
that your formerly fat friend
is getting married first
Oh wow that You know what
That is so unfair
Now I want to steal your thunder
Come on Ross Lets go have sex
I cant believe youre gonna have sex
on my engagement night
Well somebody should
Look if were gonna do this
Were not Shes just gonna think we are
I see so everybody wins
Who is it
MONICA Its Monica open up
Okay Ross stop it Please wait a minute
Ow
Yeah you like that baby
May we help you
I wanted to say I hope you have sex
and I hope you get back together
I warn you the night
you announce your engagement
Im going to announce
that Im pregnant
How is that ever going to happen
Do you want to know why
I was with Ross tonight
I know why
You dont
Okay why
Because I was sad
What do you mean
Look I am so
so happy for you guys
But you getting married reminds me
of the fact that Im not
Im not even close
Maybe I just wanted
to make myself feel better
I know that thats dumb
but you were so depressed
when Ross got married
you slept with Chandler
I dont care she slept with me
Anyway sweetie
I am so sorry I ruined your night
Im sorry I almost made you sleep with Ross
Im gonna take off
Congratulations man
Thanks
And Rachel
Yeah
ROSS
What can I say
You missed your chance
From now on the only person whos
going to enjoy these bad boys is me
We thought Phoebe would leave
But she just stayed and stayed
Thats right Im here all night
And Chandler will never get
Hey heres a dollar
Consider it a deposit
Please sing at our wedding
Oh thank you
Okay
Now who will perform the ceremony
Who will perform the cer
Oh oh
Ill pound on him in the morning