The caterer sent me this list of 1 2
appetizers I have to narrow it to six
Food Oh give me
So did Monica tell you were trying to get
The Swing Kings to play the wedding
Since when are you into swing music
Since forever I used to go all over town
listening to bands
Chandler
Gap commercial
So did you book them Did you call
I will
You want me to call
No Ill do it You stick to your job
What is your job
Staying out of the way
This is impossible
Why dont you just pick all 1 5
There were only 1 2
Oh yeah I added three
What are peanutbutter fingers
Well hello
Shes cute
Should we go try to talk to her
Sure The great thing about being engaged
Im not nervous to talk to pretty girls anymore
Could you guys help me
Yeah let me get that for you
Its really heavy
I got it
Oh
So hi Im Ross
and this is my friend Chandler
Im Kristen
Kristen Hi Are you new to the area
Because if you are
Id love to show you around sometime
I actually just moved from four blocks over
Oh
But this block is like a whole other world
Actually it does have
a very interesting history
This street is the first street in the city
to have an underground sewer system
Before that sewage and waste
would just flow
right down the street Yeah
Sometimes ankledeep
Smooth
Excuse me
Youre gonna be starving after moving
What do you say I take you to dinner tonight
Id like that
Yeah Great
Let me take this up
After you
Oh no After you
Oh my God
Am I crazy or does this totally go
RACHEL
Oh my God You look so beautiful
Thank you Rachel
But look at Monica
This is it Yeah this is the one
I cant believe I found it
Wow you look so beautiful
If I knew you Id cry
Im Monica Geller Ball like a baby
Im Megan Bailey
Have you found your dress yet
No These dresses are all so amazing
but I couldnt afford one
No I cant afford this either
Im here to figure out the one I want
then Ill get it at Kleinmans this discount place
Day after tomorrow
theyre having a huge sale
Thanks for the tip
When are you getting married
Im not I just like to try these on
I do the same thing
Im just kidding
Im getting married July 25th
Im just kidding too Ha ha
Im getting married in December
When are you getting married
May 1 5th
Ooh Its close
So whos your photographer
Jeffrey
We met with him
Did he show you nude wedding photos
Best Man Wow
I know I almost called off
my wedding Heh heh heh
Oh whos your band
My fiancé wants The Swing Kings
Youre lucky My fiancé wants
the heavy metal band Carcass
Is that spelled with a C or a K
Oh my God it doesnt matter theyre both great
Oh you know what Dont buy that here
Now that you know what you want
go to Kleinmans Get it half off
This place is so overpriced
I own this store
So does this come
in another color or
Hi You moving in or moving out
Moving in
Can I give you a hand
Okay but be careful The guy who was helping
before had to leave because he hurt his back
Boyfriend
No
Im Joey
Kristen
Wow What a beautiful name
What is it again
Kristen
Ah thats it Okay
You live around here
Yeah Yeah right down there
Let me give you a tip
Dont take a nap on this stoop
You could wake up without shoes
Ill remember that
Okay
Listen would you like
to have dinner with me tonight
I have plans tonight
How about tomorrow
Sounds great
Well where does this go
You look strong Ill take that
you grab one of the boxes
Okay Yeah
Yeah Ill get this one
WOMAN 1
Whats taking so long
WOMAN 2
Come on
So this is Brooklyn
All right listen up Theres usually only
one dress in each size
So when they open those doors
fan out
This is what youre looking for
Memorize it
When you locate the dress
blow on these all right
Three sharp blasts
When you hear it come running
Okay got it
WOMAN 1
Here he comes
RACHEL Oh theyre pushing
Dont be a baby
WOMAN 1  Out of the way
WOMAN 2 Lets go
Hey Rachel Come on
No No not it Not it Not it Ugh
Dont crowd me
This is it This is the dress
Oh my God Its perfect
Im sorry this ones taken Whoa
Megan
Monica
You came
Yeah
This is my dress
No
Yes it is You saw me wearing it
And now youll see me buying it
You freak
You wouldnt even know
about this place without me
Look you dont want to fight me
Maybe I do Im pretty feisty
Im coming Im coming
Hey
Okay Hey
Oh what do I do
What are you doing
Did you find the dress
No You gotta get me out of here
These shoppers are crazy
Weve gotta get Monica
You gotta hold my hand
Oh my God
Excuse me Excuse me
Go Go Go
Hey
Go
So Ross
how was your date the other night
Did you tell her about the magical
ride that starts with the flush of every toilet
Laugh all you want but she left me a message
saying shed like to go out again
Oh
In fact Ill go call her right now
And Ill make sure and tell her my
friend Chandler says
Hey Chandler
Hey
Sorry I didnt stop by last night
but I had a date
Joe when its 1 00 in the morning and you
dont come by Thats okay
Check it out lt was with this really hot girl
who just moved in right across the street
Really Right across the street
Yeah
When did you meet her
Two days ago
Excellent
You know Ross met somebody too
Oh yeah
Hey
Howd it go
Great Were going out again Saturday
But I found out shes
also seeing some other guy
Really
Joe what would you do
if you were in Ross situation
Well I sort of am Im dating this girl
whos also seeing another guy
But Im not too worried about it
You shouldnt be Believe me I wouldnt want
to be the guy whos up against you
I mean that doofus is going to lose
So this is nice
I wish I didnt have to go
Believe me
But I have to
By the way whats the name
of the girl youre dating
ROSS  JOEY Kristen Leigh
Bye
Well obviously only one of us
can keep dating her
Obviously So how do we decide
Well now
lets look at this objectively
I think I should date her
Uhhuh Uhhuh
Or Im the one who dates her
Thats interesting
But check this out I date her
Yeah I like that But just to go
in another direction
Okay This can go on for a while
We should order some food then
No Joey
Look why dont we
just let her decide okay
Well each go out with her
one more time
And well see who she likes best
That sounds fair
Maybe Ill take her
to that new French restaurant down the street
Wait a second
We have to set a spending limit on the date
I dont have the money to take her
to a fancy place like that
Well sorry
Thats what I do on dates
All right Well I guess Ill just have to do
what I do on dates
So lets decide on a spending limit
Yeah
Uh
And a slice
Six dollars
I was thinking more like a hundred
Okay
Can I borrow 94 dollars
Uh
I know Can you hand me a tissue
Youre out of Diet Coke
Hello
What You what
You listen here missy
What
That was Megan She booked The Swing Kings
on the day of our wedding
and said shed only
give them back for the dress
Does that mean Carcass is available
What am I gonna do Thats the dress
That is the dress
Chandler wants the band
What do I do
Figure out a way to talk him out of it
How
RACHEL
Youre out of toilet paper
Hey
Whats up
I wanted to wish you good luck
on your date
Thanks
What time are you meeting
We have 800 reservations
at Grand Merci Bistro
Thats in 20 minutes
Youd better get dressed
I am dressed
Oh well good
For me
Whats this
Did you give yourself a facial
I have an oily Tzone
Okay dude
Hey you sent Kristen flowers
Thats right
You spent 1 00 dollars
Thats the limit Youre screwed
Actually I sent the flowers before
the actual date so technically
technically I didnt break any rules
Thanks for stopping by though
Thats how its gonna be
I can break the rules too
What are you gonna do
I dont know
Im not surprised
You wont get away with this
You dont have much choice
Well see
Byebye
Yeah byebye
Hey So just a light layer
Yeah just here and there
Joey got meat sauce
on the banister again
Swing music is so out
Phoebe hes gotta be in the room
for that to work
What are you guys talking about
Were talking about The Swing Kings
and whether theyre
the right way to go
I went to a wedding
where they had swing music
and two months later
the couple divorced
Im not saying
theres any connection here
but they did tell me
thats why they got divorced
But I love swing music
But The Swing Kings
They suck so much that people actually die
at their concerts They just stop living
When Monica and I went to see them
we had fun
And theres another reason
Well what is the other reason
I dont want to say
Well you have to
because maybe its stupid
Its just while Monica and I
were dancing to them
it was the first time
I knew that
you were the woman that I wanted
to dance all my dances with
Oh crap
Our table will be ready in just a few minutes
Oh great
Is your back feeling better
Yeah its fine
I guess ahem the more muscles you have
the more they can
spasm out of control
Kristen
Joey
JOEY Hi
KRISTEN Hi
What are you doing here
I like this place
And technically technically
Im not breaking any rules so
Well Ross this is Joey
Joey Ross
Hi
Hi Its nice to meet you
I used to have a friend named Joey
I dont anymore
Our table will be ready
in a couple minutes
Sure I would love
to wait with you guys Thanks
So Joey you look familiar
Are you on TV or something
Joey doesnt like to talk about it
but hes one of the stars
of Days of Our Lives
Thats right Thats right
Dont you play a woman
A woman in a mans body
Much better
So Ross its funny because you
look familiar to me too
Have you ever been married
Yes I have
In fact just the other day
Kris and I talked about how
Ive been married and have a son
Yeah little Eric
Thats right Wait No Ben
So youve just been married
the one time then
Well um
Youve been married twice
Yes And
another time after that
Boy Im getting hungry
Ahem Hey Joey have you ever been
so hungry on a date
that when the girl goes to the
bathroom you eat some of her food
You said the waiter ate my crab cake
So Ross now why did
that first marriage break up Hm
Was it because the woman was straight
or because she was a lesbian
Do you two know each other
ROSS  JOEY No
But he seems like
a guy whod marry a woman
on the verge of being a lesbian
and then push her over the edge
Wait a minute
Were you on a poster for gonorrhea
Have you ever slept
in the same bed with a monkey
Hey you leave Marcel out of this
Fine You ever gotten stuck
in a pair of your own leather pants
Hey hey Have you ever locked yourself
in a TV cabinet VDboy
Monkeylover
Where do you think we lost her
Probably around gonorrhea
Hi honey Im home
MONICA Dont come in here
Why do you have another
boyfriend in there
MONICA
No We only mess around at his place
Its funny I started it but now its scaring me
so could you come out here please
MONICA
No Im wearing a wedding dress
You got a wedding dress Thats great
MONICA Yeah but Im not keeping it
Then why cant I see it
MONICA
Oh I guess you can
But I have to return it
so you cant like it
Okay I promise Ill hate it
Wow You look hideous
Really
Yeah Thats like the most
ugliest dress Ive ever seen
Why do you have to return it
Because it doesnt really fit
Oh by the way I booked The Swing Kings
Oh thats great Great Thanks
But that dress I mean its like ugh terrible
It makes me want to rip it right off you
Okay
But you cant rip it
Well maybe a little
Okay
Hey guys you want to look
at the song list for the wedding
Guys
CHANDLER
I thought youd be gone all day
All right whats going on
Im sorry I should probably
leave you girls alone
Laugh all you want but in 1 0 minutes
well have youngerlooking skin
Yeah
Right there
You know she could use a little
Oh nice shot Yeah
Oh Oh Oh