Okay pick a card any card
All right now memorize it
Show it to everybody
Got it
MONICA Mmhm
All right Give it back to me
Five of hearts
Real magic does exist
Oh wow
Wow Joey how do you do it
I cant tell you that No
Uh somebodys at the door
on the ceiling
Heh No thats our unbelievably loud
upstairs neighbor
He took up the carpets
and now you can hear everything
Well why dont you go up there
and ask him to just step lightly please
I have like five times
but the guy is so charming
that I go up there to yell
and I end up apologizing to him
Oh that is silly
Ill go up there
Ill tell him to keep it down
All right be my guest
RACHEL Good luck
All right all right all right
If you really wanna know how I did it
Ill show you
When you handed me back the card
what you didnt see was
I looked at it so fast
it was invisible to the naked eye
I just did it
Just did it again
Here Ill slow it down
so you guys can see it Ready
ROSS  MONICA Oh
I got it now Okay
I was at my friends downstairs
and we hear every single thing
that you do
PHOEBE
Oh Ha ha Thank you
Hey
Anybody got a length of rope
about 6 feet long with a noose at the end
Honey whats the matter
I just saw Janice
ALL
Aw
She was at Rockefeller Center
skating with her husband
She looked so happy
I almost feel bad
for whipping that kids pretzel at them
I remember the first time
I saw that girl Katherine after we broke up
She was walking with her friend Donna
just laughing and talking
God it killed me
Yes but you ended up having sex
with both of them that afternoon
Sorry I just
Any excuse to tell that story
Hey Chandler theres a party tomorrow
Youll feel better then
Oh You know what Im gonna be okay
You dont have to throw a party for me
Its Joeys birthday
Oh well then if anybody
should have a party it should be him
Shh I cannot believe shes still up there
Okay well
he totally screwed up the punch line
You know its supposed to be
Hows that coffee coming dear
Yeah Right away Mr Kaplan
Im not supposed to drink coffee
It makes me gassy
I know
Ill bet youre thinking
Whats an intelligent girl
who wants to be in fashion
doing making coffee
Ah Ah Ha ha
Oh ha ha You got me Heh
Dont think I havent noticed
your potential
Well Ive got a project for you
thats a lot more related to fashion
How does that sound
Oh That sounds great
Come on over here sweetheart
Thank you so much Mr Kaplan
I need these hangers separated ASAP
Youre welcome
RACHEL Oh God I hate my job
I hate it I hate my job
I know honey Im sorry
Oh I wanna quit
but then I think I should stick it out
Then I think
why would such a person stay
in such a demeaning job
just because its remotely related
to the field theyre interested in
Gee I dont know Rach
Order up I got a Yentl soup James Beans
and a Howdy hold the Doody
Oh Honey come on Im sorry I didnt
I dont mind paying my dues
Its just how much am I gonna learn
about fashion
by walking Myra
the arthritic seamstress
to the bathroom
RACHEL
Hi Is my misery amusing to you
Im sorry I was just uh Ha ha
Its not funny This is actually my job
Oh believe me Ive been there
I had to sort mannequin heads
at Mannequins Plus
Oh Well then so Im just gonna go back
to talking to my friend here
You can go back
to enjoying your little hamburger
Uh just one other thing
Ahem Yes
I work at Bloomingdales
and I might know of a job possibility
if youre interested
Do you want my pickle
GUNTHER
Hey guys
Hey Gunther
Hi
Youre going out on a date
with the noisy guy upstairs
Well hes very charming
I know hes too charming
But if you go out its gonna make it
so much harder for me to hate him
Well youre just going to have to try
All right Joey
Where are the JellO shots
I dont know
Chandlers supposed to be passing them
Chandler
Well somebodys feeling better
Stick out your tongue
Take off your shirt
Oh my
JOEY Oh my God
How many of these did you have
These are pure vodka
Yeah JellO just like Mom used to make
The most unbelievable thing
happened to me today
Hi
Im having lunch at Monicas
and this guy starts talking to me
and he works for a buyer
at Bloomingdales
and theres an opening in his department
So I gave him my phone number
and hes gonna call me this weekend
to see if he can get me an interview
Wow Ha ha
I know
What so this guys helping you
for no apparent reason
Uhhuh
And hes a total stranger
Yeah His name is um Mark something
Ah Sounds like Mark Something
wants to have some sex
What
Im just saying why else would he just
swoop in out of nowhere for no reason
To be nice
Hey Joey are men ever nice
to strange women for no reason
No only for sex
Thank you
So did you tell Mark Something
about me
I didnt have to because I was wearing
my I Heart Ross sandwich board
and ringing my bell
Ah Uhhuh
SISTERS
Joey Happy birthday
Hey
Okay how many of that girl
are you seeing
How hammered are you Huh
These are Joeys sisters
Hi Joeys sisters
Hey
Hey Hey
What are we drinking over here
Oh well I have a vodka
and cranberry juice
No kidding
Thats the exact same drink I made myself
right after I shot my husband
Wow
Okay I dont know how to talk to you
What are you doing
Im taking my exgirlfriend
off my speed dialer
SISTERS
Aw
No no no its a good thing
Why must we dial so speedily anyway
Why must we rush through life
Why cant we savor the precious moments
Those are some huge breasts you have
Hi
Yeah heh So um I heard about
this Mark guy that Rachel met today
Oh yeah isnt that great
Oh yeah
So uh yeah pretty good
He sounds like a nice good guy
Oh he is And he is so dreamy
I mean you know what
When he left I actually used the phrase
homina homina homina
Thats excellent
So hes just a nice guy
You really think this Mark doesnt want
anything in exchange for helping you
Well I assume Ill have to take showers
with him
But you know thats true of any job
MONICA
Uhoh
How you feeling
Well my apartment isnt there anymore
because I drank it
Whered you get to We lost you
after you opened up all the presents
Yeah I ended up in the storage room
and not alone
ALL
Woohoo
Really
Aah
No woohooing No woohooing
Why what happened
I fooled around with Joeys sister
Well thats not the worst part
What is the worst part
I cant remember which sister
You see what men do
Dont tell me men are nice
This is men
Are you insane
Joeys gonna kill you
Hes actually going to kill you dead
Okay You dont think I thought of that
How can you not know which one
RACHEL I mean thats unbelievable
I mean was it Gina
Which one is Gina
The dark big hair
with the airplane earrings
MONICA
No no no thats not Gina thats Dina
See You cant tell
which is which either Blah
We didnt fool around with any of them
Blah Blah
Veronica Look its gotta be Veronica
The girl in the red skirt
I definitely stuck my tongue
down her throat
That was me
Oh When Ive been drinking
sometimes I tend to get overly friendly
And Im sorry
Thats okay
Thats all right
PHOEBE  ROSS Thats okay
Can I talk to you for a second
Hey Joey
Hey
Come on
Why cant we talk in here
with witnesses
I just got off the phone with my sister
Uh which one
Mary Angela
Yeah
Now which one is she again
Ask Chandler
Hes the one who fooled around with her
She told me you said
you could really fall for her
Now is that true or are you just
getting over Janice by groping my sister
Its gotta be the first one
Really
Thats great
You and my sister sitting in a tree
Yep Im in a tree
Did he call Did Mark call
No honey Im sorry
But the weekends not over yet
Oh my God Is that Phoebe
Guess theyre back from their date
Ah
Music Very nice
Uhhuh Oh
Oh my God
RACHEL
So how are you
I am good I finished my book
Oh yeah Whats it about
I dont remember
Do you wanna take a walk
Yeah I do
Dear Mary Angela
Hi hows it going
This is the hardest letter
Ive ever had to write
What the hells the matter with you
How do you think Joeys gonna react
when he finds out
you blew off his sister with a letter
Thats the part where you tell him
that I moved to France
when actually Ill be in Cuba
All right look look
youve got to do this yourself okay
In person At least you know her name
You just go to the house
and you ask for Mary Angela okay
When whichever one she is
comes to the door
take her for a walk
you let her down easy
Okay
What if Mary Angela comes to the door
and I ask for Mary Angela
Where in Cuba
Joey what What are you doing here
Waiting for my grandma
to finish my laundry
What about you
Uh Im here to see Mary Angela
You are so the man Come on
Now look listen Listen
You gotta be cool because my grandma
doesnt know about you two
You do not wanna tick her off
She was like the sixth person
to spit on Mussolinis hanging body
Yeah
Wheres Mary Angela
Shes right in there
Okay
ALL
Hey Chandler
I cant believe Mark didnt call
Its Sunday night and he didnt call
Bummer
Yeah right Look at you
Youre practically giddy
No Im genuinely sorry
the Mark thing didnt work out
Look Rach
I want only good things for you
Wait a minute
Why dont you just call Mark
Who says you have to sit here
and wait for him
Youve got to make stuff happen
Yeah but you dont
wanna seem too pushy
Honey its not pushy
He gave her his home number
Wha He gave you his home number
as in like to his home
Yeah And you dont mind if I call
because you only want good things for me
Thats right good things
That is what I said
Ahem Hello Mark Hi its Rachel Green
Ha ha Oh no Dont you apologize
Yeah Ill hold
He left my number at work
He was gonna get it but he was helping
his niece with her report on the pioneers
Aw
That is so made up
Yeah Oh my God Tomorrow
Thats No its perfect
Oh God Thank you so much
Great Bye
Oh I got the interview
Oh yay
There you go
He even offered to meet me for lunch
and prep me for it
Oh that is amazing
Yeah
Well if I know Mark and I think I do
Id expect nothing less
I gotta figure out what Im gonna wear
High collar and baggy pants say
Im a pro
Yeah right Okay Ill see you guys later
Woohoo
Okay
You go get them
What did I do to you
Did I hurt you in some way
What
Why dont you call him
Well thank you very much
Now hes gonna prep her
You know prep her as in what you do
before you surgically remove the boyfriend
Are you crazy
Oh am I Am I Am I out of my mind
Am I losing my senses
This dreamy guy is taking my girlfriend
out for a meal
MONICA
Ross you know this isnt even about you
This is about Rachel
and something happening for her
Uhhuh
MONICA Even if youre right
What if he wants to sleep with her
Does that mean he gets to
No but
I mean dont you trust her
Well yeah
Then get over yourself Grow up
You grow up
This tiramisu is excellent
Did you make it Mary Angela
No I did
Well its yummy
So uh Mary Angela do you like it
Of course Its her favorite
So um hmm
Mary Angela
whats your second favorite
More of Grandmas tiramisu
Oh would you just please
give me your recipe
because this is great
Its topnotch
That dies with me
So will I
Excuse yourself and go to the bathroom
Oh no I was just squinting
That doesnt mean anything
Just do it
Will you excuse me I have to um
Hey
Finally I thought wed never be alone
Can I just tell you something
I have not stopped thinking about you
since the party
CHANDLER
Mm Mm
Look I may have jumped the gun here
Whoa
Uh Ahem
I just got out of a relationship
And Im not really in a
In a commitment kind of place
So Me neither
God Mary Angela was right
You do have the softest lips
Aah
Youre not Mary Angela
No Im Mary Therese
This is so bad
If youre not Mary Angela then who is
I am
Oh its so bad
Joey
CHANDLER No Joey No Joey No Joey
Whats going on
Youre it Now run and hide
Its no big deal
Chandler was just kissing me
because he thought I was Mary Angela
What How could you do that
How could you think she was Mary Angela
I wasnt sure
which one Mary Angela was
Look Im sorry okay
I was really drunk
and you guys all look really similar
I say punch him Joey
Yeah punch him
Yeah kick him
We should all calm down
because you know
your brothers not gonna punch me
Are you
Well that is usually what I would do
But I never thought
youd be on the receiving end
How could you do this
Joey if you wanna punch me go ahead
I deserve it
But I just want you to know that I would
never soberly hurt you or your family
Youre my best friend
And I would never do anything
like this ever again
So what
I say punch him Punch him
Yeah punch him
Come on punch him
No No Im not gonna punch Chandler
Ill do it
JOEY No you wont
Look he knows he did a terrible thing
and I believe him
Hes sorry
But you got one more apology to make
All right
You gotta apologize to Mary Angela
Okay Absolutely You got it
All right
Cookie now you can punch him
What
Hey
Hi
What are you doing here
You know
this buildings on my paper route so
Oh Hi
ROSS Hi
How did it go
Oh well the woman I interviewed with
was pretty tough
but you know
thank God Mark coached me
Once I started talking about the fall line
she got all happy
Im so proud of you
Me too
Listen Im uh
Im sorry Ive been so crazy
and jealous and
Its just I like you a lot so
I know
ROSS Yeah
Yeah
MARK Rachel
Hi Hi
Hi Mark
I just talked to Joanna and she loves you
You got it You got the job
What
Oh I did
Yes
Aah
Oh my God
Congratulations
Oh Wow
So Phoebe
PHOEBE Hmm
How was your date
Oh well you know Ha ha
Yeah I do know
Ick You were eavesdropping
Eavesdropping
Pheebs the ceiling tiles were falling down
Oh Im sorry
But I really like this guy
and I think he really happens to like me
Aw
Yay
Maybe hes just jumping on a pogo stick
and he really likes it
Maybe the pogo stick likes it too
All right thats it
He cannot do this to Phoebe
This guys gonna get the buttkicking
of a lifetime
But is he a big guy
Well all go Come on
Thanks you guys Thank you
CHANDLER Dont worry
God I hope they kick his ass
Honey Im sorry
You know if its any consolation
he really did sound
like he was having more fun with you