Hey
MONICA Hey
I saw the Porsche parked out front
Can I get the keys
Ill take that bad boy for a spin
Ross drives it When I ask
you say youre the only one allowed to
Hes my brother plus he drives
so slow he couldnt hurt it
Its a car Monica not a rocket ship
Whatever Ross
Just replace the bulbs in the brake lights
after youre done
Hey
ROSS Hi
Saw the Porsche Looking good
When can I take it out again
You let Joey drive it
Ive never driven it Not once
Okay once Okay I drive it all the time
So much for the you can drive it
but dont tell Rachel plan
Wow I cant believe you lied to me
I can fix this Monica Rachel thinks
all you can talk about is the wedding
I wont let you drive the Porsche
because youre a terrible driver
There That wasnt about the wedding
If you want a ride in the Porsche
Ill take you around the block
You got a couple hours
Whew that was a brisk ride
Take the top down did you
Only way to fly
Give me the keys Monicas wrong
Im an excellent driver
Youre fast and irresponsible
That adds up to a bad driver
In high school that added up
to head cheerleader
Did you see the look
that girl just gave me huh
She mustve seen me cruising
in the bad boy
Shes checking out your beehive
What
Give me a brush
Give me the keys
No way
Well no brush
Fine lt doesnt matter
If I remember correctly theres a comb
on the floor of the bathroom
Alimony
We still havent gotten an RSVP
from your dad
Oh right Um maybe thats because
I didnt send him an invitation
Chandler hes your father
He should be at your wedding
I dont even know him
I havent seen him in years
And when he finds out he wasnt asked
We dont run in the same circles
I hang out with you guys and he
stars in a drag show in Vegas
Ooh I think I want to trade circles
You dont want him there
Nobody will stare at the bride
when the grooms fathers
wearing a backless dress
Heh so what
As long as hes not wearing
a white dress and a veil I dont care
I think I need to do some shopping
Ah
Ooh nice
My God
What do you think youre doing
Just washing the windshield
Theres no way Ill let you drive this car
Just hand over the keys
Oh
Oh ahahah
Do not start this car
Okay okay I will give you 20 bucks
if you get out of this car right now Hey
Look
If youre so freaked out get in the car
With you Yeah right
All right
Okay okay okay
What are you doing Get in front
In the death seat
Hey guys
Hi sweetie
Ready to go
My purse is at Mons Ill be back
Wait a minute
What
Oh
Ooh
Oops
Whoa oh that one kept going
So you and Phoebe huh
How long have you been going out
A month
Wow We ought to get to
know each other better
Sure Id like that
Yeah So uh
Whats your name
Its Jake
Joey
Do you like the Knicks
Yeah big fan
Me too Theres a game Tuesday
Do you want to go
Great Let me make sure
Im not doing anything Tuesday
Here
Whats this
Your suitcase Were going to Vegas
Are you serious Eloping
No more stupid wedding stuff
No more these flowers these flowers
Think of the money well save
Were not eloping I love the flowers
Can our wedding be bigger please
Were going to see your dad
I want to get to know my fatherinlaw
We already went over this and I won
No you didnt Honey just so you know
Now that youre marrying me
you dont get to win anymore
Forget it I dont want to go
I dont want to see him
I know your dad embarrassed you
All kids are embarrassed
by their parents
You need a new word
for what I went through
In high school
he came to all my swim meets
dressed as a Hollywood starlet
Its hard enough to be 14
Youre skinny wearing Speedos
your mom promised youd grow into
You look up in the stands
Theres your dad cheering you on
Dressed as Carmen Miranda
wearing a headdress with real fruit
that hell later give to your friends
as a healthy snack
The point is that he was at every one
of your swim meets cheering you on
Thats a pretty great dad
He had sex with Mr Garibaldi
Whos Mr Garibaldi
Does it matter
Chandler
Youre not 14 anymore okay
Maybe its time you let that stuff go
If hes not at your wedding
youll regret it for the rest of your life
Okay but Im just doing this for you
Yes
I never get to win anymore
How much did you ever win before
Pheebs
Hey
You know how uh when youre wearing pants
and you lean forward
I check out your underwear
Yeah
Well when Jake did it
Mmhm
I saw that he was wearing
womens underwear
I know They were mine
Oh
No no wait Thats weird
We were goofing around
and I dared him to try them on
Thats weird
Im wearing his briefs right now
Thats kind of hot
I think so too And that little flap
Great for holding my lipstick
I wouldnt know about that
Jake says that womens underwear
is actually more comfortable
He loves how silk feels against his skin
Next hell say your high heels
are good for his posture
Theres nothing wrong with Jake
He is all man
I think more than you
He looked like a real lumberjack
in those pink lacies
Only a man completely secure
with his masculinity
could walk around in womens underwear
I dont think you could
I am secure with my masculinity
Okay whatever
Youve seen my huge stack of porn
Where they at Where they at
God I forgot how much I love driving
I have got to get my license renewed
You dont have a valid drivers license
Pull over right now
Youre so tense You just gotta relax okay
Okay Just need to relax All right
Just need to relax
What are you Thats not funny
Stop horsing around
I am not horsing around okay
I am Porscheing around
Uhoh
Stay calm Nothing will happen
Youre not in that much trouble
Really You think so
Im talking to myself Youre going down
I can feel something inside me say
Has someone taken your order
Oh yeah She did Um he did She
Im sorry Im new I dont
Mmhm
I just ordered a beer
Youre straight I get it
If we called your dad
wed have better seats
I dont want him to know
were here yet Im not ready
He wont be too happy to see me either
Why not
I dont know if I told you this
but hes kind of tried to contact me
a lot over the last few years
What
Yeah Hes made phone calls
written letters
He even came to New York
I said I was too busy
Its very Cats in the Cradle
I dont want to get into it
Here we go
Ladies and gentlemen
please welcome the incomparable
Helena Handbasket
Hello darlings
And theres Daddy
Okay Switch places with me Come on
Ill go under you go over
Yeah Ill get right on that
Ugh come on
What No Hey Rach come on
Im sure we wont get arrested for this
God
Hi officer Was I going a little too fast
Oh my God
Can I see your license please
Oh yes absolutely
Its weird I had a dream last night
that I was stopped by a policeman
And then he um
Well I probably shouldnt tell you the rest
Your license
Yes Ahem Here you go Officer uh
Handsome
Its Hanson
Oops sorry My mistake
Dear Lord
Wow
Here it comes
This is a great picture
Ah
Really You think so
You know I had just rolled right out of bed
You look phenomenal
She should lt was taken 1 0 years ago
You know youre probably um
Probably wondering about the old date
Yes I am Youre an Aquarius huh
Ill bet youre a Gemini
No
Taurus
Virgo
No
Sagittarius
Yep
I knew it I knew it
You wont speed anymore right
I wont speed
Promise to take care of this
I promise
Let him drive Does he have a license
Yeah
Can he handle a stick
Oh well
I can handle a stick
I feel pretty
Oh so pretty
I feel pretty and witty and
AUDIENCE
Gay
That cant be your father
Ive been saying that for years
Oh my God
What
Thats Mr Garibaldi playing the piano
For Im loved
By a pretty wonderful boy
Hello and welcome to the show
I see some of our regulars in the audience
And a couple of irregulars
Hes coming into the audience
Relax Youll be fine
Oh much better Youre invisible now
Where are you from
Bakersfield
Im sorry
No no I heard Im just sorry
Ill meet you back at the hotel
Look a standing ovation already
So early in the show
Turn around darling
Let me see your pretty face
Can we have our drinks please
Uh waiter tress
Hey Pheebs
Hey
Check it out
Huh
How much of a man am I
Wow nice Manly and also kind of a slut
You know Im beginning to see
what Jake was talking about
Uhhuh
The silk feels really good
And things arent as smashed down
as I thought they would be
Thats great
You have so many more choices
than with mens underwear
Bikini French cut thong
And the fabrics cotton silk lace
You know what Ive always
wondered about Pantyhose
The way they start at your toe
then they go all the way up to
I should go take these off
I think its important you do
Mm
Whats your name
Chandler
What an unusual name
You must have had terribly
fascinating parents
Oh theyre a hoot
And who is your friend
Im Monica
Monica Where are you from
New York
Im not very fond of New York
Queens I like
Ooh what is this
sparkling something honey huh
Actually Monica and I are engaged
Really
Congratulations
Whens the big day
In two weeks
I see
Well I wish you both
a lifetime of happiness
So youre bald
Wait wait
Wed really love it if you could be there
Really
I know it would make me happy
maam
Then I wouldnt miss it for the world
Oh Im getting all misty here Ha
Youd think I was having my legs waxed
or something
You okay
Yeah
Thanks for making me do this
Before we go on with the show
I want to say to the bride and groom
how lucky they are to have
found each other
In every life a little rain must fall
Fortunately
in my life
Its raining men
CHORUS
Hallelujah
Its raining men uhhuh
Amen
When I was growing up
I played the one on the far left
CHORUS
And its raining men amen
Remind me to introduce you to someone
Who
Fourth gear
What
What does he want
I wasnt doing anything
Maybe he saw your hands slip briefly
from the 1 0 and 200 position
Maybe its uh Sergeant Sagittarius
coming back to flirt some more
Its a different guy
Good evening officer
Do you know how fast you were going
Uh no I dont but it could not
have been more than 60
Youre right lt was 37
Youre not ticketing me
for driving too slow are you
Thats right
You know officer I uh
I had the weirdest dream last night
Oh my God
Your license please
You dont want to hear about my dream
Officer
Pretty
Its Petty
Ill be right back with your ticket
You have a son
I know I know
Feel better
Yeah Much Heh
Listen uh
Not that Im insecure about
my manhood or anything but uh
I need to hook up with
a woman right now
I understand
Yeah okay
Hey Hi
Hi
You look familiar Do I know you
I dont think so
Maybe its because Im on television
Im an actor on Days of our Lives
Wow Really
Fourfifty please
Oh let me get this
These are for you