We learned one thing CHEESE
Cheerleaders and high explosives
dont mix
You can say that again Mac
I couldnt have done it alone
Youre a genius
Oh yeah Well how come I cant get
my VCR to stop blinking 1 200
What did you guys think
CHANDLER Hey the phone
MONICA I got it I got it
Hello
Hold on Joey its your mom
Its Mommy
ROSS Aw
PHOEBE Thats nice
JOEY
Ma so what did you think
Well
that was um okay
It wasnt the best
That was one
of the worst things ever
and not just on TV
What should we say
The lighting was okay
You got lighting last time
Lighting is mine
I have costumes
That means Im stuck with
So we were watching you in there
and you were sitting right here Whoa
What about you
I dont know
I cant lie to him again
Oh no I No
Im just gonna press
my breasts up against him
And say nothing
Uhhuh yeah thats right
Wow my folks really liked it
What did you guys think
It wasnt that good
Do you think that your favorite animal
says much about you
You mean behind my back
Oh youll never believe
what happened to me today
I am sitting in my office
JOEY You guys
Guess what my agent just said
Im in the middle of a story here
Sorry you finish
Im sitting in my office
and guess who walks in
Im gonna be on two TV shows
BOTH
Thats great
Joey
You werent finished
Yeah Guess who walks
into my office is my story
Ralph Lauren walked into my office
Uh if youre starting another story
at least let me finish mine
Its the same story
Uh wow its really long
Ralph just came in to tell me
that hes so happy with my work
that he wants me to be the new
merchandising manager for Polo retail
PHOEBE
Aw
Still get a discount on wedding gowns
Yeah
Im so happy for you
These really are
the days of our lives
What
Well since you ask ha ha
They want me back on
Days of our Lives
I get a big pay raise
Oh hey
Ill be playing Drake Ramorays
twin brother Stryker
MONICA  PHOEBE
Ooh
I get to hire my own assistant
Well I got a head rush
from standing up too fast
You were at this job four years
Thats right
This is all very impressive Hilda
Um I just have
one last question for you uh
How did I do Was this okay
What
Ive never interviewed anyone
Ive never had anyone work for me
When I was a kid we had a maid
but this isnt the same
No dear its not
And I know that
Well thank you so much for coming in
Nice to meet you
Good meeting you
RACHEL
All right
Im a total pro
Hello
Wow Huh um
Hi yes Im sorry
The models are down the hall
Im here about the assistant job
Really
Okay well then all right
Well just have a seat there
Um so whats What your name
Tag Jones
Uhhuh go on
Thats it Thats my whole name
Thats your whole name
Of course
Okay lets just have a looksee here
I havent worked in an office before
I dont have much experience
What are you talking about
You got three years painting houses
two whole summers
at TGI Fridays
Its lame I know
But Im a goaloriented person
eager to learn
Just hold on a second please
Its for Human Resources Everybody
has to Would you stand up
Ha ha no no no
Hey
Shh shh shh
Anyway I should go
Okay Bye
Hey sweetie
Hi sweetie
What was with all the whispering
I cant tell you Its a secret
Secret Married people arent
supposed to have secrets
We love and respect
one another too much
Aw
But still no ha ha
We should tell each other everything
I dont have secrets from you
Really So tell me what happened
to Ross junior year at Disneyland
No I cant do that
Ill tell you what Phoebe said
Okay
So ahem Ross and I
are going to Disneyland
We stop at this restaurant for tacos
When I say restaurant I mean a guy
a hibachi and the trunk of his car
So Ross has about ten tacos
Anyway were on Space Mountain
and Ross starts to feel a little iffy
Oh my God He threw up
No he visited a town
a little south of throw up
Oh my God
What was Phoebes secret
Um Nancy Thompson from Phoebes
old massage place is getting fired
Oh
Thats it I gave up
my Disneyland story for that
Hm thats right You lose sucker
Please still marry me
You have an assistant right
Did she call
You told her I was sick right
Always tell her I am sick
I dont know
How do you decide who to hire
I have it down to two people
One has great references
and a lot of experience
And then theres this guy
What about him
I love him
Hes so pretty I want to cry
I dont know what to do
Come on you know what to do
You hire the first one
Dont hire assistants because theyre
cute Do it because theyre qualified
Uhhuh
I hear you You make a lot of sense
Can I just say one more thing
Look how pretty
Let me see
Oh my God
Oh But no
No You cant You cant hire him
because its not professional
Um this is for me yes
Okay youre right
Ill hire Hilda tomorrow
Dumb old perfectforthejob Hilda
Let me see
Wohaow
Dont show this to Monica
And dont tell her
about the Wohaow
Ha ha hey Joey
Hey Terry
Nice to see you again
Been a while
Funny these halls look smaller
than they used to
Its a different building
So
Stryker Ramoray huh
When do I start
How about right now
Okay
Here are the audition scenes
I thought you
were offering me the part
Why
I was Doctor Drake Ramoray
Strykers twin brother
Who looks more like me
than me right
Everybody has to audition Ha ha
You know Terry
I dont really need to do this
I got my own cable TV series
with a robot
Im sorry Joey
Thats the way it is
Well
I guess you think
youre pretty special huh
Sitting up here in your fancy
smallhalled building
making stars jump
through hoops for you huh
Well you know what
This is one star whose hoop
This is the star the hoop
This hoop
I was Doctor Drake Ramoray
Hi Tag What are you doing here
I came to thank you for not laughing
in my face yesterday
I noticed there were no plants
so I brought you your first
There is a plant in your office
Kind of
Right
So I guess I shouldnt put
good at noticing stuff on my résumé
Oh
Thank you
Anyway
Im guessing you hired somebody
Well
Gotcha
Thanks again for meeting with me
But I hired you
What
Yeah you got the job
Youre my new assistant
I am
Yeah
I cant believe it
Ha ha me either
First I need you to go downstairs
find a woman named Hilda
and tell her to go home
Hey
Hey good youre home
Always nicer to hear than
Oh crap you again
Hey sweetie I made you a surprise
Oh yeah
Yeah tacos
Ever since that story
Ive had such a craving
Did you not understand the story
Hey
Hey whats up
Ah nothing Just figuring out
what to do for dinner
Hey ooh whats that Dinner stuff
You making dinner
No
CHANDLER
Shh
Whats over there Tacos
No No
Theyre just uh Theyre
Theyre ground beef smileys
Uh those are tacos
Excuse me Mr Mexico
Either way Ill pass
Still cant eat those
Ha ha
Whats so funny
Im not laughing
You told her
Nancy Thompsons getting fired
Okay okay I had food poisoning
Its not like I chose to do it
Its not like I said
What would make this ride more fun
Right Youre right Im sorry
I shouldnt be laughing
I should be
laying down papers for you
How could you
I had to Were getting married
Married couples cant keep secrets
I I guess Monica should know
about Atlantic City
Duude
What happened
Chandler and I are in a bar
Did you not hear me say Duude
and this girl
is making eyes at Chandler
So he goes over to her and uh after
a minute or two I see them kissing
Youre thinking hes not the type
to go to bars and make out with girls
And youre right
Hes not the type
to go to bars
and make out with girls
You kissed a guy
Oh my God
In my defense it was dark
and he was a very pretty guy
Oh Mon I laughed so hard
Hoho so hard we had to throw out
your underwear again
Whatever dude You kissed a guy
Hi
Hey
Hows Hilda working out
Oh my new assistant
is working out Yes
She happy she got the job
My new assistant is very happy
that I hired my new assistant
Hello
Oh hey Can you hang on a second
Its the producers at
Mac and CHEESE
if youll excuse me for a minute
Hey funny you should call I was
just looking over next weeks script
Canceled
Like theyre taking it off the air Oh
All right Ill see you Monday
Were not even shooting them anymore
All right Bye
They canceled Mac and CHEESE
Oh sorry
Oh sorry Joey
Why would they do that
It was a good show right
You want to tell secrets
Okay in college
Ross used to wear leg warmers
All right Chandler entered a Vanilla Ice
lookalike contest and won
Ross came in fourth and cried
Oh my God
Oh is that funny
You find that funny
Maybe Chandler should know
your secrets too
Ha ha
Oh I I already told him everything
You shush
Once she was sent to bed
without dinner
so she ate the macaroni off
a jewelry box shed made
Ross stayed home every Saturday night
to watch Golden Girls
Monica couldnt tell time
until she was 1 3
Its hard for some people
Of course it is
wow
Chandler wore my underwear to work
Oh Im sorry I couldnt think
of any more for Ross
In college Chandler got drunk
and slept with the lady
who cleaned our dorm
That was you
Whatever dude You kissed a guy
How could this happen to me
Yesterday I had two TV shows
Today I got nothing
Wait a minute
what happened to Days of our Lives
Uh well they might be a little mad
at me over there
What happened
Well maybe I got a little upset and
maybe I told them where they could go
Joey why would you do that
Because They wanted me to audition
You an actor Thats madness
Rachel Greens office
Tag
Hi who was that
Nobody I was just practicing
Really
Hi
Hi Rachel Greens office
You must be Hilda
RACHEL Ahem
Hes Tag This is Phoebe
Phoebe can I see you for a sec
PHOEBE Mmhm
Phoebe
Great name
You like that
You should hear my phone number
Okay
So you hired yourself
a little treat did you
I know how it looks
but I am telling you
You cant get involved
with your assistant
I know that and I know hiring him was
not the smartest thing Ive ever done
But from now on
I swear this is strictly professional
Yes
Hey Rachel
RACHEL
Hi
Cute assistant Whats his story
Is he
Gay Yeah
Hey Terry
TERRY
Joey Tribbiani
Surprised your big head
could fit through our small halls
TERRY I gotta go Joey
JOEY Wait Terry Look uh
Im really sorry about before
I was an idiot thinking Im too big
to audition for you
Give me another chance
I cant
Wait Terry please
Look I just lost my other job okay
You have no idea
how much I need this
Please help me out
For old times sake
This guys been in a coma
for five years Its hopeless
Its not Dr Stryker Ramoray
is a miracle worker
Here he comes
Good morning
Drake its your brother Stryker
Can you hear me
DIRECTOR
And cut
Im back baby
You know in my defense um
there was no glitter on
the macaroni and very little glue
And in my defense
the cleaning lady came on to me
Do you have trouble telling time now
No
Quick what time is it
Time to kiss a guy
What are you laughing at Pampers
You know when I said
married people
should share everything
and not have any secrets
Yeah
That was stupid Lets not do that
MONICA
Oh
Absolutely
We should keep the stuff we told
each other secret from everyone else
CHANDLER Ha ha
Yeah definitely
Okay ha ha
If youll excuse me
Im gonna hang out with people
who dont know
the Space Mountain story
Then Id steer clear of Phoebe
Man
Not that you would but I wouldnt
hang out with the guys at my office
Hi
Do you have a minute
Sure Whats up
I got asked out twice today
while I was at lunch
by guys
Really
TAG Yeah
Did you tell someone that I was gay
Oh did you not want people
to know that
Im not gay I especially wouldnt
want you to think I was gay
Why is that
I dont think I should say
Oh you can say
Come on I dont want you to feel
like you cant tell me things
Okay
Well
Yeah
Id love to ask out
your friend Phoebe
Yeah shes gay