Mom would you relax
That was 10 blocks from here
and the woman was walking alone at night
I would never do that
Mom come on stop worrying
This is a safe street
This is a safe building Theres nothing
Aah Oh my God
What are you doing in here
Mom I gotta go I gotta go
Oh my God
Okay
Thats fine you just read the paper
Im gonna get a pot
Its not for you
Okay thats fine
Read the Family Circus
enjoy the gentle comedy
Oh my God Oh my God Oh my God
Ugh Oh God Oh God
Its open you guys
Hi
Hi Can I help you
Im looking for Phoebe
does she still live here
Uh no she doesnt
But I can get a message to her
Great Uh just tell her
her husband stopped by
Her what Aah
Hey how did you do that
This is unbelievable Pheebs
How can you be married
Im not married married
you know
He was just a friend and hes gay
and he was from Canada
and he needed a Green Card
I cant believe you married Duncan
I mean how could you not tell me
We lived together
we told each other everything
Im sorry Monica but I knew if I told you
youd get really like judgmental
and would not approve
Of course I wouldnt approve
You were totally in love
with this guy who hello was gay
I mean what the hell were you thinking
See And you thought
shed be judgmental
Okay I wasnt in love with him
I was just helping out a friend
Please When he left town
you stayed in your pajamas for a month
And I saw you eat a cheeseburger
Well didnt you
I might have
I cant believe you didnt tell me
Come on
Like you tell me everything
What have I not told you
Ooh I dont know Um
how about the fact that the underwear
out there on the telephone pole is yours
from when you were having sex
with Fun Bobby on the terrace
What
Wait a minute Who told you
You are dead meat
I didnt know it was a big secret
Oh its not big Not at all
You know kind of on the same lines as
say I dont know having a third nipple
You have a third nipple
You bitch
Whip it out Whip it out
Yeah yeah
No come on Theres nothing to see
Its just a tiny bump Its totally useless
Oh as opposed to your other
multifunctional nipples
I cant believe you
You told me it was a nubbin
Joey what did you think a nubbin was
I dont know You see something you
hear a word I thought thats what it was
Let me see it again
Yeah show us your nubbin
Joey was in a porno movie
If Im going down
Im taking everybody with me
Oh my God
You were in a porno
All right all right
I was young and I just wanted a job okay
But at the last minute
I couldnt go through with it
So they let me be the guy who comes in
to fix the copier but cant
because theres people
having sex on it
Wow
That is wild
So whats it shaped like
Is there a hair on it
What happens if you flick it
So uh does it do anything
you know special
Why yes Ross pressing my third nipple
opens the delivery entrance
to the magical land of Narnia
You know in some cultures having
a third nipple is actually a sign of virility
You get the best huts
and women dance naked around you
Huh Are uh any of these cultures
per chance in the TriState area
You know you are so amazing
Is there anything you dont know
Ooh Julies so smart Julies so special
Look honey I wanted you to hook up
with Ross as much as you did
But hes with her now
Youre just gonna have to get over it
Oh Im going to have to get over it
God see I didnt know thats what
I had to do I just have to get over it
Whoa
Sassy lady
Where are you going
Um Im gonna go meet Duncan
Hes skating tonight at the Garden
Hes in the Capades
The Ice Capades
No no the Gravel Capades
Yeah the turns arent as fast
but when Snoopy falls Funny
I cant believe youre dressing up for him
Youre setting yourself up
all over again
Okay no
For your information Im going to see him
so I can put all those feelings behind me
And the reason Im dressed like this
is because I think its nice
to look nice for your gay husband
Darn it were all out of milk
Hey Chandler will you fill me up here
Oh I see I see
Because of the thirdnipple thing
Okay sweetie Ill see you later
Bye
See you later Rach
Byebye Julie
Hey
Hey come on cut it out
What
Can I ask you something
Sure
Eh
What
Come on talk to me
Okay
Whats the longest youve been
in a relationship before
having the sex
Why Whos not
Are you and Julie not
Are you and Julie not having sex
Well
Technically
No
Wow
Is it because shes so cold in bed
Or is it because shes kind of bossy
makes it feel like school
No No Shes great And its not
like we havent done anything
I mean we do plenty of other stuff
Lots of other stuff like
No no no
Dont need to know the details
No its just
Its me
You know Ive only been
with one woman my whole life
and she turned out to be a lesbian
Uhhuh
So now Ive got myself all psyched out
Its become like this
this thing and I
You must just think Im weird
No No no no I dont think its weird
I think I think um in fact
In fact you know what I think
What
I think its sexy
Sexy
Let me tell you something
As a woman
there is nothing sexier
than a man who does not
want to have sex
No kidding
Oh yeah In fact you know what Id do
Id wait
Youd wait
Yes absolutely I would wait
and wait
Then Id wait some more
Really
Oh yeah
I dont care how much she tells you
she wants it I dont care if she begs
she pleads she tells you
shes gonna have sex with another man
That just means its working
Women really want this
More than jewelry
Hi
Phoebe
Tada
Hi
Ah look at you You look great
Do I Thank you
So do you Sparkly
Thanks
So
Wow This is pretty wonderful huh
Mr Major Capades Guy
I remember when you were just like
King Friday in Mr Rogers Ice Is Nice
You always said Id make it
Yeah well you know
Im kind of spooky that way Woo
God I missed you
Im gonna get changed
Okay
Um now
What
Pheebs
Oh Right Okay
Olé
What
The Matador so
Olé Ha ha
Sweetie can you hold this for a second
Sure
Thanks
Uh Julie
Yeah
Sorry you had a paleontologist
on your face
But uh its gone now Youre all right
Hi everyone
Hi
Oh listen listen
I wanted to thank you
for uh our little talk before
Oh God no problem
So youre gonna go with the waiting thing
Well I was going to
but after I talked to you I talked to Joey
Good Ahem What did he say
Basically he told me to get over myself
and just do it
So I thought about what you said
and about what he said
And well his way
I get to have sex tonight so
What is this in my pocket
Why its Joeys porno movie
Pop it in
Im fine with it I mean
if youre okay watching a video
filled with twonippled people
Great People having sex
Thats just what I need to see
Whats wrong with people having sex
Well
Well um you know
these movies are offensive
and uh degrading
to women and females
And uh the lightings
always unflattering
And
Monica help me out here
Hell I wanna see Joey
So is there like a story
or do they just start doing it right
Oh Never mind
Okay now wait a minute That is the
craziest typing test Ive ever seen
All I say is she better get the job
Looks to me like hes the one
getting the job
Shh Hey here I come Here I come
See Im coming to fix the copier
I cant get to the copier Im thinking
What do I do What do I do
So I just watch them have sex
And then I say Heres my line
You know thats bad for the paper tray
Nice work my friend
Thank you
Wait you see me again
Hang on the guys butts blocking me
There I am There I am There I am
So um So whats up
You came to see me yesterday
Oh yeah um
All right
I kind of need a divorce
Okay
How come
Um actually Im getting married again
What
Oh God
I dont know how to tell you this
Im straight
Yeah I know
I dont understand I dont understand
How can you be straight
I mean youre so smart and funny
and you throw
such great Academy Award parties
I know Thats what I kept telling myself
But you just reach a point
where you cant live a lie anymore
So how long have you known
I guess on some level
I always knew I was straight
I thought I was supposed
to be something else
You know Im an ice dancer all my
friends are gay I was just trying to fit in
And um And theres actually a woman
Her names Debra
Oh
Well is she the first
that youve been with
Well Ive never told you this
but there were one or two times
back in college
when Id get really drunk
and go to a straight bar
and wake up with a woman next to me
But I told myself it was the liquor
and everyone experiments in college
Sure
But now I know I dont have a choice
about this I was born this way
I dont know what to say
I mean you know
youre married to someone for six years
and you think you know him
And then one day he says
Oh Im not gay
Im Im still me
Why couldnt you just have
figured this out six years ago
You know
it still smells like monkey in there
Well that saves us the conversation
Well this has been great
but Im officially wiped
Me too We should get going
No
No I mean No Come on you guys
Come on look its only 1130
Lets just talk We never just
hang out and talk anymore
Rachel thats all we do
Maybe thats all we do
What about Julie
Well you have been in our lives
for nearly two months now
and we dont really know you
I mean who is Julie
I mean what do you like
What dont you like
We want to know everything
Well heh that could take a while
So
I mean who here does not have
the time to get to know Julie
I got the time to get to know Julie
I got time yeah
Uh Rach ahem I know her pretty well
Can I go
Thats fine
Okay Julie so lets start with
your childhood What was that like
Well in a nutshell
Ahahah
So um have you told your parents
No but itll be okay Theyre pretty cool
My brothers straight so
Here you go
You know what
I just have one more question Um
If you had figured this out sooner
and um I had been around
do you think I would have been
the one who
No no Thats all right Dont tell me
I dont think either answer
would make me feel better Here
I love you Phoebe
So your brothers straight huh
Seriously
And my secondgrade teacher
was Miss Thomas
and my firstgrade teacher
was Mrs Cobb
Ahem Mrs Gobb
No Cobb Like cobb salad
Hmm okay
Now what exactly is in a cobb salad
Im going home
Boy that Julies a talker huh
Good night
Whew
So its pretty late Youre probably uh
not still planning on
Oh No no I am
Oh
Well hey are you nervous
No no I uh
I have done it before
Well okay I mean
how are you gonna handle it
Are you gonna talk about it beforehand
Are you just gonna pounce
I uh I dont know
I guess Im just gonna
see what happens
Okay Good luck
What Uh
What
Nothing I mean um
It is your first time with her and you know
if the first time doesnt go well
well then thats pretty darn
hard to recover from
Okay now Im nervous
Maybe you should put it off
No I dont want to put it off
God Im just I spent last year
being so unbelievably miserable
And now Im actually happy
You know I mean really happy
I just dont wanna
I dont wanna mess it up you know
I know
Yeah
Im sorry
No its not your fault
Right
Maybe it doesnt have to be this tough
Maybe you were on the right track with
that whole you know spontaneous thing
I mean women really like that
Really
Yeah I mean you know if
I mean if it were me Id you know
want you to
What
I dont know catch me off guard
You know with like a really
good kiss
You know really
sort of um soft at first
And then maybe um
brush the hair away from my face
And then look far into my eyes
in a way that lets me
know something
amazing is about to happen
Uhhuh
And then I dont know then
youd pull me
really close to you so that
So that Id be pressed up you know
right against you
And um it would get kind of
sweaty
and uh And blurry
And then its just happening
Oh
Thanks Rach Good night
Oh God
Good morning
Well somebody got some last night
Twice