Hey
What you guys doing
Monicas making us watch Old Yeller
Why are you guys upset
Its Old Yeller Its a happy movie
What
What are you talking about
Come on Happy family gets a dog
Frontier fun
Pheebs what about the end
Oh when Yeller saves the family
from the wolf and everyones happy
Thats not the end
Yeahhuh Thats when my mother would
shut off the TV and say The end
What about when he has rabies
He doesnt have rabies
He has babies
Thats what my mom said
Uh Phoebe I dont think shed want you
to see whats about to happen
Why Whats about to happen
Ive never seen this part
Hey Travis what you doing
with that gun
Oh no
No no Travis put down the gun
No no hes your buddy
Hes your Yeller
No The end The end
Okay what kind of a sick
doggy snuff film is this
Have you guys eaten Uh Richard and I
just finished and weve got leftovers
Chicken and potatoes
What am I wearing
Actually nothing but rubber gloves
One of these times youll really
be naked and we wont come over
I got a leg three breasts
and a wing
How do you find clothes that fit
Oh hey Monica We got a question
All right yes I see other women
in the shower at the gym
And no I dont look
No not that one
Were figuring out who to bring
to the Knicks game
Ross cant go so its between my friend
Eric Prower who has breath issues
and Dan with the poking
Did you see that play
You want more beer
Is that Spike Lee
Ha ha okay
Why dont you ask Richard
Uh Richard if you had an extra
ticket to the Knicks game
and you had to choose between
a friend who smelled
and one who bruises you
who would you pick
Wow
Being a huge Knicks fan myself
I think you should take someone
whos a huge Knicks fan
Okay
Thats Eric
Glad to be of help Matches
I meant why dont you
take Richard to the game
Eh
What
I dont know
Come on
He keeps his fingers to himself
and hes always minty fresh
Richards really nice
Uh we just dont know him really well
Plus hes old
er than some people
But uh younger than some buildings
So what hes a little older
Big deal
Hes important to me
If you ask him
he might take you in his Jag
How do we say yes
and make it seem like its not
just to ride in the cool car
Okay this could be tough
Okay okay okay Monica
Well bring him
but only if he takes the Jaguar
Ooh you almost had it
No no youre fine Youre fine
Hello ha ha
Hey
Hi honey Oh
You are not gonna believe
what happened
We were playing on the floor
and he grabs the table
and he pulls himself up
He pulled himself up
Standing man
Im sorry you missed it
but I did tape it if you wanna see it
Uh we know
He already did it last week
You can watch our tape if you want
Ah see I dont believe this
I missed the first time of everything
The first time he rolled over
the first time he crawled
What else Has he spoken
Is he driving
Does he have a favorite liqueur
He is getting closer
on the talking thing
He cant quite say mama yet
but once he said Yemen
See I dont know
Im so sick of missing stuff
I want him for more than a day
I want him for a whole weekend
Listen I feel
That would be great
Really I had a whole speech prepared
Oh shoot that wouldve been fun
Oh look did you just see that
Did you see He just waved
He just waved
Hes never waved before
Yes he has Very good
Hey
Hey Pheebs What you got there
Love Story Brians Song and
Terms of Endearment
Wow all you need now
is The Killing Fields
and some guacamole
and you got yourself a party
I talked to my grandma
about the Old Yeller incident
and she said my mom used to not
show us the ends of sad movies
to shield us from
the pain and sadness
You know before she killed herself
Hey
Wheres Richard
Did you ditch him
After we stole his lunch money
and gave him a wedgie
Whats the matter with you
Hes parking the car
Did you guys have fun
Your boyfriend is so cool
He let us drive his Jaguar
Joey for 12 blocks Me for 15
Wow
He must like you best
Oh what about when he tipped the guy
who showed us to our seats
You never even saw the money
Hey Chandler thanks for
showing us to our seats
Ha ha youre welcome
Hey Joey thanks for parking the car
No problem ha ha
Hey Chandler
I think they get it
Theres the man
Hey
Hey youre getting better
Huh Ha ha
Im gonna keep this
Okay
He kept my dollar
Your first weekend without Ben
What are you doing
Ah were going to
colonial Williamsburg
A woman I went to college with is
the first female blacksmith there
Theyre a little behind the times
in colonial Williamsburg
Ha ha Well look I better go
before Mommy starts weeping
We love you
Bye Mommy
Have a good time
Okay Ben
Ross
Yeah
Look
Joey do you know
we can see you from here
How come Richard looks cooler
with one of these
You may wanna light it
and lose the spatula
Its cute you trying
to be more like Richard
Not like him per se
Just not unlike him
Its the artist formerly known
as Chandler
Im just trying something here
you know
Why didnt you grow a mustache
Oh we flipped for it
I got the cigar
he got the mustache
If we both grew them
wed look like dorks
You really sidestepped
that land mine
I promised Richard
wed meet downstairs
Youre meeting Richard
Ranger game
Didnt he tell you
He said he was going out with the guys
I didnt know that was you
You hear that
Were the guys
With that mustache
he reminds me of Aunt Sylvia
Thank you
Hi were visiting
Yay
Its Ben and his dada
Dada
Can you say dada
Aw
Im telling your mommies you said it
so you might as well
No luck huh
No
A while ago
I got a seh out of him
which I thought might turn into
sehcondary caregiver but
Would you uh hold him for a sec
I gotta take this off
Oh yeah sure okay
There we go
What are you doing
Im holding Ben
Yeah well hes a baby not a bomb
Okay
Hold him like youd hold a football
This is how I would hold a football
Here Here There we go
Sorry Im not very good with babies
I havent been around them
I mean you know since I was one
Ha ha
Its all right No big deal
Really
Youll feel different
when its our baby
What
You think about stuff like that
Uh yeah I mean
Actually I kind of think
that well have two babies
Two babies
You know a boy and a girl
Hopefully the girl will come first
so Ben wont feel competitive
Then whats gonna happen
We wont wanna raise kids in the city
so well move to Scarsdale
Scar Uhhuh
Well be far enough from our parents
so we dont have to see them
but close enough
that they can babysit
And yes I know the taxes are
a little higher than Nassau County
but the school systems great
Wow Ha ha
Wow thats great Great
Okay wow You know what
Hmm
Im off my break now So uh
Um here You take this
And um
Im gonna go pour these
very nice people some coffee
Okay
Look at that I dont have a pot
I dont have a pot
Maybe Ive got one at home
Or in Scarsdale
Hey is that a door
Rach
Hey
Hey Pheebs Whats happening
Oh okay murder cancer soccer teams
eating each other in the Andes
You watched the movies
Uhhuh
What is happening to the world
I mean
No no because ET Leaves
and Rocky loses Charlotte dies
Charlotte who
With the web The spider
She dies She has babies and dies
Its like Welcome home
from the hospital Thud
You wanna feel better
Yeah
Okay
Here Watch this
Its a Wonderful Life
Yes Ive heard of this
So you cant lose
Its there in the title
Wonderfulness is baked right in
I fell for that with
Pride of the Yankees
I thought Id see a film
about Yankee pride
And boom The guy gets
Lou Gehrigs disease
Uh the guy was Lou Gehrig
Didnt you kind of see it coming
Watch that Itll restore
all your faith in humanity
Hey big guy Game time
Hey Be right there
Theres a game
I just got my PikUp Stiks
back from the shop
Bring your nerves of steel
Its the basketball playoffs
Um I appreciate this but you dont
have to hang out with them for me
They have each other
Oh no honey I mean dont worry
I like hanging out with them
Theyre different than my other friends
They dont start sentences with You
know who just died shoveling snow
All right thats great
Then just go
Go Knicks
Uh its the college playoffs
Oh
Then go Vassar
Uh theyre not in it
Okay then just go
Okay
Ugh why does this bother me
so much
Im not one of those people who wants
to spend 24 hours a day together
Sure
He just doesnt have much free time
What do I do
Does it matter Youll just die
or divorce or blow your pets head off
Ugh
Me too
Rachel I got a question Richard
made plans again with the guys
Ross made plans for the century
Im gonna go read Cosmo
Maybe theres something helpful in it
If not I can learn how to do a bikini
wax with leftover Christmas candles
Okay
What happened back there
I dont know You tell me
One minute Im holding Ben
then Ive got two kids
Im living in Scarsdale
complaining about taxes
Well Im sorry
I think about stuff
Youre at work youre assembling bones
your mind wanders
Youve planned out the next 20 years
Weve dated for six weeks
You never think about our future
I think about whose apartment
well sleep at tomorrow
and where well have dinner
next Saturday
I do not think about
our childrens names
You know what our
childrens names will be
Ha ha no
No I mean you know I read a book
and there was a girl named Emily
And I thought that might be good
What was the book
The Big Book of Childrens Names
Okay Ross Ross
Okay listen
What we have is amazing
But I do not want
everything decided for me
I spent my whole life like that
Its what I had with Barry
Thats a reason I left
I like not knowing right now
Sorry if that scares you but if you
wanna be with me deal with that
Okay fine
Thank you
Were not done
I didnt know that
Youre with a guy who wont stop
planning his future with you
He knows well end up together
If that scares you tough
Youll have to deal with that
I will
Good because I love you
Oh yeah I love you too
Thats the first time weve said that
Yes
Im gonna kiss you
You better
Hey
Oh thanks for the great movie tip
Did you like it
Oh yeah
I dont know if I was happier when
George Bailey destroyed the business
or um Donna Reed cried or when
the pharmacist made his ear bleed
Ill give you the ear thing
but wasnt the ending wonderful
I didnt watch it
I was too depressed
It kept getting worse
It shouldve been called
Its a Sucky Life And Just When You
Think It Cant Suck Anymore It Does
Kick save And
denied
He gets it back
Pass to the middle lines it up and bam
Yes
Could that shot be any prettier
Man you are incredible
We had a table in college
Oh really I didnt know they had
foosball in the 1800s
Nice mustache At puberty
that thing will really kick in
Not to sound too Florence Henderson
but dinners on the table
One more point
Score
Now can we go
Uh
Thats why we dont let her play
Is everything all right
Mmhm
Uhoh
Oh hey dont be mad at him
Its our fault
Im sorry weve been hogging his time
Hes just really great
to hang out with
Well
No seriously
We just talked about this
He is so much cooler than our dads
Our dads are okay and all
but Richard is just
Ow ow ow
What are you kicking me for
Huh Im trying to talk here
Uh you guys see me as a dad
Oh yeah
No
Youre just clearly not familiar
with our young persons vernacular
When we say dad we mean buddy
We mean pal
Uhhuh yeah
No seriously Joeys my dad
Monicas my dad
Ive even got some dads down at work
Thats fine
Well your other dad and I are gonna
go have a romantic evening
Ill just see you kids around
Nightynight
Youre not a dad
I cant believe you got us
into trouble
So are you okay
Yeah
Just
I feel like Im about a hundred
I thought I was just one of the guys
Come here
Ill make you feel like
one of the guys
Mm
For a really cool guy
you suck at foosball
I was killing them
Yeah well they suck too
Ha ha
Hmm
You take the poopy diaper
and put it in the poopy diaper pail
Calling it a poopy diaper
doesnt make this process any cuter
Hello
Its us
Come on up
Ill get his stuff together
Okay we can do this now
cant we Ben
Yes we can
There I did it
Ha ha I did it
Ooh look at that
Oh it stays on and everything
Hi
Im sorry What did you just say
Did you just say hi
Oh my God Ross
Ben just said hi
What
What the word hi
No my Uncle Hi
Great And I missed that too
I miss everything
Oh Im sorry I guess I just
bring it out in him
Where is he
We missed you
We missed you so much
Come here Ben ha ha
Guess what
Ben just said his first word
What did he say
Something about hi
Thats so exciting
Mommys so proud of you
Hi Hi
You know actually
its more like hi
Hi
This could go on for a while
Youre right
Weve got a cab waiting
Well this was fun
We should do it again sometime Ben
What do you say
Okay
All right so Ive got him
Tuesday
Bye you guys
Take care
Bye Ben
Bye
Did he just say bye
He said bye
You said He said bye to me
Yes he did
Oh
Suddenly Im seeing him
go off to college
Weve gotta go
Weve got that cab downstairs
See you later
Bye
Oh
Ha ha
Bye
Oh
Wow Look at this nice deep hole I dug
Hey Bert
isnt this a nice hole here
Okay ahem
Ben this is the part where Ernie buries
Bert in the sand and cant find him
Now Ive looked ahead on the tape
and he does find him again
But before that happens
theres some rough going for a while
But I think we can handle it
And theres just the alphabet
but we know that ends well so
Here we go
Bert Bert
Bert
What happened to my friend Bert
He was here just a moment ago
Oh no My old friend Bert is lost
Mm
Im so glad youre here