Do you realize this is the last time
well be here in the coffeehouse
as six single people
Whats happening to the coffeehouse
Oh Okay
From now on its you four
and me and the missus
The little woman The wife
The old ball and chain
Old
The young hot ball and chain
Much better
We gotta go
Where
Get the dress and lunch with mom
Joey you too
I just heard lunch
Yeah I can go Sure
Actually Im glad theyre leaving
I need to talk to you
about something
Whats up
This may be a little awkward
If you need money its a bad time
Im buying dinner for 1 28 people tomorrow
No its not that
Im not gonna say this
as your friend
but as Monicas older brother
But youre still my friend
Not for a few minutes
Right now are you still my best man
No
Do I still call you Ross
Okay
You guys are getting married
and I couldnt be more thrilled
But as Monicas older brother
I have to tell you this
If you ever hurt my little sister
if you ever cause her
any unhappiness of any kind
I will hunt you down
and kick your ass
What Im serious
Dude Stop it Im not kidding
I hear what youre saying
and thanks for the warning
No problem
So are we friends again
Yeah
Okay
Ahem You wont believe what Monicas
brother just said to me
What you doing Mon
Im listing all the things that
could go wrong at the wedding
So I can be prepared
Mmhm What are they
The dresses wont get picked up
veil gets lost
and Im missing something blue
Those are all the things Im responsible for
I had to go with the odds
Hey You guys
Remember I had that audition a while ago
and I didnt get that part
The commercial
No
That play
That other play
No
The movie
Yes
The one about the pilot and his dog
No
But man that one hurt
This is the one about WWI soldiers
Oh yeah
Back then we called it
The Great War
It really was
A guy they wanted backed out
and now they want me I start shooting today
Congratulations
Todays the rehearsal dinner
Ill be done by then
Oh Then way to go
you big movie star
See you
Im off to fight the Nazis
Wait Joey We fought the Nazis
in WWII not WWI
Whoa Okay
Who was in WWI
Go ahead
Youre gonna be late Go Go
Yeah Ill see you
Who did we fight in WWI
Mexico
Yes Very good
Hey Joey Were ready
Yeah me too
Richard were ready for you
Joey Tribbiani Richard Crosby
is playing Vincent
Im doing my scenes with you
Nice to meet you
I cant believe this Incredible
You just won an Oscar
No I didnt
I think you did
I think I lost three times
Uh cookie Would you
No
Okay Were about an hour away
from getting the scene lit
So uh can you guys run it a couple times
Yeah sure
All right Lets do it
And action
We have to find the platoon
Forget the platoon The platoon is gone
What
The platoons dead Face facts Tony
Whatll we do
We have no reinforcements or food
Theres food in the basement
Potatoes and some pasta
Hang on Joey you keep
touching your face
Something wrong
No
I uh
I thought it might be
a cool character thing
Hes a face toucher
I dont think so
Lets take it back
to Richards last lines Action
We may not have any weapons
but we still have food
Potatoes pasta
and a few tins of tuna
Honey we gotta go
Okay
Heres a question
you never want to ask
My dad just called and wants to know if he can
borrow one of your pearl necklaces
Did he say what kind of neckline
hes wearing
No
Ive only met him once
but Im guessing plunging
He is more of a If youve got it
flaunt it kind of father
I dont have anything
but let me see if Rachel does
Yes include more people
in this
Hey Do you realize that tomorrow
were gonna be getting married
I have a date tomorrow night
I cant believe we made it
You dont have to sound so surprised
Im sorry but
Nothing
What
Well honestly
Ever since we got engaged
Ive waited for you to flip out
Honestly Me too
Really
Yeah
I think that something
stupid will come up and Ill
go all Chandler
But nothing has
Im so glad
Thank you for staying
so calm during this
Its made me stay calm
I couldve been worse
Okay
Ill be right there
Hi if youre calling before Saturday
youve reached Monica and Chandler
But if youre calling after Saturday
youve reached Mr and Mrs Bing
Please leave a message for
the Bings
MONICA Maureen
Hi
Gosh This is my cousin Maureen
Were the Bings
Hi You guys look so beautiful
Mr and Mrs Bing
Wow Monica
So you know I had my
olderbrother talk with Chandler
What is that
Well I
I told him that if he ever hurt you
I would hunt him down
and kick his ass
What is the matter with everybody
Im serious
I would kick his ass
Ross please my makeup
Hi
Chandler
Mom
Thanks for wearingsomething
Ohh This is so exciting I thought we
screwed you up too much for this
Just think soon there will be
lots of little Bings
I cant believe I have to go back to work
after this and get spit on again
Youre lucky At least the people
who spit on you are famous
Who spits on you
I dont wanna talk about work
Mrs Bing These are my parents
Judy and Jack Geller
Its lovely to meet you
Are you his mother or father
Jack
What Ive never seen one before
Dad theres Ross
Go talk to him
I didnt even have a chance to act
as if Im okay with it
Hello all
HiDad
Hi Mr Bing
Nora
Charles
Its so great to see you both here
Yes
Although we may be seeing
too much of some people
Arent you too old
to wear a dress like that
Dont you have too much penis
Oh my God
Of course you can kick his ass son
You could kick anyones ass
you want to
Thanks you guys
Rach Rach
Yeah
Do me a favor Talk to Chandlers dad
and keep him away from Chandlers mom
Yeah but I dont know what he looks like
He is the man in a black dress
Hi Im Rachel a friend of
Monica and Chandlers
Im Amanda
Oh I get it
A man duh
Could I have your attention
Im Ross Geller
Dr Ross Geller
Dad please As I was saying
Im Dr Ross Geller
Uh and Im the best man
And this marriage
is doubly special for me
um because not only is the groom
my best friend
but uh the bride is my little sister
Shes the greatest sister
a guy could ask for
Please join me in raising a glass
to the couple were
here to celebrate
To the Bings
ALL To the Bings
Im gonna steam my dress
Who will make sure nothing
happens to it
Ill do it
Who wants it Anybody
I said Ill do it
Nobody
All right Ill do it myself
Im not gonna screw it up
Youre right Im sorry
You were a big help tonight
And thanks for putting my grandmother
in the cab to get to the hotel
Of course Thats what Im here for
Okay Sorry
Ugh Pssh
What grandmother
Where have you been
Taking my parents to the hotel
Going back to work
Yeah
Nice shades
If I wear these in my scenes
I wont get spit in my eyes
And if I remember correctly RayBan
was the official sponsor of WWI
Great All right
Ill see you later
All right
Wheres Chandler
I think hes in Rachels room See you
Chandler
Hey
Hi
Is Monica here
Shes steaming her dress Why
I think Chandlers gone
What
He left that
Tell Monica Im sorry
Oh my God
Whats up
Tell Monica Im sorry
Tell her yourself
Oh my God
Chandler just left though
Maybe its not what we think
Maybe its
Tell Monica Im sorry
I drank the last of the milk
Or maybe he was writing to tell
her that hes changed his name
Tell Monica Im Sorry
It means he freaked out and left
Dont be so negative
Good God isnt it possible that
Sorry is sitting in there right now
Phoebe I think Ross is right
What are we gonna do
Im gonna have to go find him
and bring him back
You make sure Monica
does not find out okay
But if you dont find him
and bring him back
I am gonna hunt you down
and kick your ass
I will find him
Joey Can you
go through these lines with me
Oh man they just redid my makeup
Just the last two pages
All right
I found the picture
Picture What picture
The picture of my wife
I found it in your pack
Could you lower the script
I dont want to
I need to see your face so
I can play off your reaction
Okay look
I know youre great
and play all those Shakespeare guys
but youre spitting
all over me man
Of course I am
You know youve been spitting
Thats what real actors do
Enunciation is the mark
of a good actor
And when you enunciate you spit
Wow Didnt know that
Thanks Okay check it out
Picture What picture
Have you seen Chandler
No I havent seen him
Damn
Hes getting married tomorrow right
Yes Dont worry Everythings fine
See you at the wedding
I wasnt invited
Then well see you
the day after tomorrow
Mom Dad
What are you doing here
You kids talk about this place so much
we thought wed see what the fuss is all about
I see why the girls like coming here
Why
The sexy blond behind the counter
Gunther
She just added him to her list
Your list
Of people were allowed to sleep
I know what the list is
Sit down have a cup of joe
I cant Im sorry
If you see Chandler
tell him Im looking for him
And if you see Rita Moreno
let her know Im looking for her
DIRECTOR
Action
I found the picture
What picture
A picture of my wife in your pack
You went through my personal property
Why do you have a picture of Paulette
in your pack
Because Vincent we were lovers
for two years
DIRECTOR
Cut Wonderful
Great scene huh
You were awesome
In that last speech you soaked me
Tomorrows call sheet
Im not working tomorrow
You are now
No you gotta get me out of it
I have plans Important plans
Still no word from Chandler
Oh man
But they found the grandmother
wandering down 5th
Okay well theres one down
Im getting married today
I cracked a rib but I dont care
Todays my wedding
My day is finally here
She might not even notice hes gone
Im gonna start getting ready
We cant let her start getting ready
This is too awful
Shell be in the gown
and he wont show up
Then shell
have to take off the gown
Stop it You cant do this here
Im sorry Im sorry
Its just so sad
Pull it together
She cant see you like this
Shell know somethings wrong
I know I know
Theres no tissue
Can you grab me some toilet paper
Oh thats gone too
This is Monicas bathroom right
I found one
Okay
Thank you
Oh God
Can I have another one
Sure
Do you need some floss
I cant imagine what will happen
if he doesnt show up
Heres a whole bunch
Shell be at the wedding waiting
and people will be whispering
That poor girl
Then shell have to come back here
and live alone
Oh my God
What
There was a pregnancy test
in the garbage and its positive
Monicas pregnant
So I guess she wont be totally alone
NARRATOR
Next time on Friends
Weve gotta tell her that hes gone
No we cant
Shes gonna start getting ready soon
Cant you stall her a little
Im never gonna get married
Weve just got one short scene
Its just you and Richard and hes a pro
Are you drunk
No
Yes you are
All right
Hows Chandler
Great
Where are you
On the set
This is turning into the worst
wedding day ever