Hey We are so in luck
Treeger said we could have
all this cool stuff from the basement
Wait right there
Oh no no Im paddling away
Huh
Wow Really
We got all this rusty crap for free
Uhhuh
This and a bunch of bubble wrap
and some of it is not even popped
Could we be more white trash
How desperate am I
Oh good thing Chandlers not here
He always wins at this game
I just told my mom
Id cater her party for her
How come
Because I need the money
And I thought itd be a great way to get rid
of that last little smidgen of selfrespect
Come on I think this is a good thing
I dont think Mom wouldve hired you
if she didnt think you were good
at what you do
You dont have to stick up for her
She cant hear you
Hey um do you guys have any juice
Just pickle
Hey uh Rach Funny story
I bumped into Joanna
on the street yesterday
My boss Joanna
Wow that must have been awkward
Well no Actually she asked me
if I wanted to get a drink
You uh didnt say yes to that did you
Ha ha No No
Hello Rachel
Well not at first
What is she doing here
I dont understand
Last time you went out with her
you said she was a dud
I think I judged her too quickly
And this time we were able
to take the relationship to the next level
Well last time I almost got fired
You must end it You must end it now
Its not like this is an everyday occurrence
for me
I mean usually Im pretty much
in there by myself
RACHEL
Chandler
Promise me you will end it
Okay I promise Ill end it
Thank you
But I hope you know
what Im giving up for you
Because shes not just the boss
in your office
You know what I mean
Yeah
Oh sorry I knew what he meant
Hows the hired help
Doing great Quiches are coming along
Whats this Blue nail polish
Yeah I thought it was cute
Ha Its what your grandmothers hands
looked like when we found her
Let me ask you a question
Why did you hire me
Oh well Richard raved
about the food at his party
of course you were sleeping with him
Then I heard the food at that
lesbian wedding was very nice
I assume you werent sleeping
with anyone there
Though
at least that would be something
Oh my God Did you hear that
She hired me because
she thinks Im good
Okay I didnt hear that
Yeah She didnt hire me out of pity
It wasnt so she could pick on me
in front of her friends
She actually thinks Im good
Wow And hey its cool if youre a lesbian
Ha ha
Good afternoon Are you
the decisionmaker of the house
Uh
Do you uh currently own
a set of encyclopedias
No no but uh try the classifieds
People sell everything in there
Actually Im not buying Im selling
Let me ask you one question
Do your friends ever have
a conversation
and you just nod along
even though youre not really sure
what theyre talking about
Im telling you
its totally unconstitutional
I hear you Yeah it is
I totally agree
I think he deserves a Nobel Prize
GROUP
No
It was like the Algonquin kids table
Excuse me Im sorry
You havent said anything
for about two and a half minutes
Are you at all interested
Yeah Yeah Yeah oh yeah Come on in
Come on
Thats weird
What
Your nails
Oh I know I never wear fake ones
I just did it so my mom wouldnt
give me grief about biting them
No I meant its weird that
you only have nine now
Oh my God
Wait a minute
I had them when I put
Oh my God Its in the quiche
Oh my God
Okay dont panic
Im gonna go to the store
get you another set of nails
No one is gonna know
and youre gonna look great
Oh Oh its because theyre gonna eat
Thats the problem
Honey dont bite your nails
Okay uh please dont freak out
Um but theres a blue fingernail
in one of the quiche cups
And theres no way to know which one
And whoever finds it wins the prize
Ha ha Im not freaking out
Why are you laughing
Its nothing Its just that now
your father owes me 5
Ha ha What you bet Id lose a nail
Oh no dont be silly
I just bet that Id need these
MONICA Frozen lasagnas
Mm
You bet that Id screw up
So all that stuff about hiring me
because I was good was
No that was all true
This was just in case you
pulled a Monica
You promised Dr Weinberg
youd never use that phrase
Honey come on Have a sense of humor
Youre never able to laugh at yourself
Thats right Ha ha
My mom doesnt have any faith in me
Oh thats hilarious
I dont get it
No I have faith
No You have lasagnas
Oh the ruined quiches are ready
It just doesnt feel
like were breaking up
No we are Im sad
Okay
Yes
Uh can you wait till tomorrow All right
Unbelievable
Thanks
No no That was my boss I have to go
Okay
What are you doing
Im getting dressed
Why
When I walk outside naked
people throw garbage at me
Wait I want to show you something
What is it
Just a little gag gift somebody gave me
Put your hands together
Youre not the boss of me
Yeah you are
Hmm Saucy
Ill be back in two minutes
Youre uh
Youre going to leave me like this
Knowing youre here waiting for me
I think thats kind of exciting dont you
Okay but if you dont come back soon
theres pretty much nothing
I can do about it
Oh
Hi I brought you back a macaroon
Oh great Ill keep it in my butt
with your nose
Thats weird She locked the door
You know why
Shes got the Christmas bonus list in there
I saw her working on it this morning
Okay swear you wont tell
But when Mark left
he gave me a key to Joannas office
You want to see the list
SOPHIE Yeah
Hi
How are you
Hello Joanna
s office
Im sorry I may be a little longer
How little
A couple hours I feel awful
Look this isnt funny
You get back here now
I cant
Why not
Im in my boss car
What
Uhoh tunnel
Rachel could I see you for a moment
Okay heres the situation Ahem
The keys to the cuffs
are on the back of the door
Could you be a doll
and grab them and scoot on over here
and unlock me
And on a totally separate subject
that is a lovely pantsuit
You promised you would
break up with her
I did break up with her
She just took it really really well
And the fact that you were jeopardizing
my career never entered your mind
It did enter my mind
But then something happened
that made it shoot right out
You know what Chandler
You got yourself into those cuffs
you get yourself out them
No no no
I cant get myself right out of them
You must have me confused
with the Amazing Chandler
Come on you have to unlock me
She could be gone for hours
and Im cold and
Ugh Chandler All right This is it
You never see Joanna again
Never
You never come into this office again
Fine
You give me back my Walkman
I
I never borrowed your Walkman
Well then I lost it You buy me one
You got it Here we go
Come on This is great
Aw
Does it hurt
No I just always see guys doing this
when they get handcuffs taken off
Hello sweet pants
Wait a minute
What are you gonna tell Joanna
About what
When she sees that youre gone shes gonna
know I let you out and Im gonna get fired
Ill make something up
Im good at lying
I actually did borrow your Walkman
No theres nothing to make up
Shes gonna know I have a key to her office
Ive gotta get you locked
back the way you were
Oh I dont think so
Well this is much better
So heres somebody interesting Joey
What do you know about Van Gogh
Uh he cut off his ear
And
Im out
He painted that
Wow Thats pretty nice
I thought he cut off his ear
because he sucked
What else you got in there
Lets see uh
Where does the Pope live
In the woods
Wait wait thats the joke answer
Actually its Vatican City
Now uh what do you know about
uh vulcanized rubber
Spocks birth control
You need these books
Hey
Hi
This used to be your room
Wow Oh you must have been in
really good shape as a kid
Oh Im such an idiot
I cant believe I actually thought
she could change
Look who cares what your mom thinks
So you pulled a Monica
Oh good Im glad thats catching on
Why does that have to be a bad thing
Just change what it means
You know go down there
and prove your mother wrong
You finish the job you were hired to do
and well call that pulling a Monica
What
Okay um if a kid gets straight As
his parents would say
Yeah you pulled a Monica Ha ha
Oh or a fireman saves a baby and they go
Yeah no he pulled a Monica
Or someone hits a home run
and the announcer says
Yeah that ones out of here
Because some things dont change
All right Ill go down there
But Im not gonna serve the lasagna
Im gonna serve something that I make
Wait
Ooh
Oh Wow
Wow my breasts are really strong
RACHEL
Chandler
Chandler please I have to get you
locked up back the way you were
Im so going to lose my job
Shes very private about her office
Now I know why
Hey look
Youre in trouble either way okay
If she comes and sees me
locked to this instead of the chair
shes gonna know you were in here
So you might as well just let me go
Ill clean your bathroom for a month
Still wouldnt be clean
All I want is my freedom
Foot rubs for a month
Freedom
Ill take all your photos
and put them into albums
Freedom I want my freedom
Why wont you hear me
Sophie help me
Help me
Sophie sit
God would you just calm down
Im going to say this for the last time
Would you please just
Wow theres a lot I didnt know
about vomit
In a minute
So what do you say Joey
You get the whole set
of encyclopedias for 1 200
That works out to just 50 bucks a book
Twelve hundred dollars
You think I have 1200
Im home in the middle of the day
and I got patio furniture
in my living room
I guess theres a few things
you dont get from book learning
Well uh what can you swing
How about zero down and zero a month
for a long long time
You dont have anything
You want to see what I got Okay
I got a baby Tootsie Roll
a movie stub keys a Kleenex
a rock
and an army man
Okay I get the picture
Uh thanks for your time
And a fifty
Huh These must be Chandlers pants
For 50 bucks you can get one book
What will it be A B C
I think Im gonna stick with the V
I want to see how this bad boy turns out
Heh
I uh will buy and wrap
all of your Christmas gifts
No
Oh
I uh Oh Ill squeeze you
fresh orange juice every morning
With extra pulp
Yeah
No
Ive got it
You dont have it
I have so got it
Theres gonna be rumors about this
Theres no way to stop it
Sophie knows
Monica and Phoebe know
How do Monica and Phoebe know
Oh I called them
When they ask me what I saw
I can be very generous
or very stingy
Go on
I can make you a legend
I can make you this generations
Milton Berle
And Milton Berle has
Oh Not compared to you
Well
Theyre not even touching the lasagna
Really
Oh they love your casserole
Yes
Its hard to believe just a little while ago
this was nothing but ingredients
Everyone seems to like your dish
And you
I thought it was
quite tasty
So if everyone liked it and you liked it
that would make this a success
Which would make you
A bitch
Well I was going for wrong
but we can use your word
Yes well I was wrong
And I have to say
you really impressed me today
Wow
Um you might even say
that she pulled a Monica
She doesnt know we switched it
And the next time you cater for me
there will be nothing but ice
in the freezer
Well that really means a lot
Oh Mom dont bite your nails
Hello
GROUP Hey
Hello Chandler
I love you
Hey whats going on
Oh
No he doesnt
Two hours that lasted
So did you break up with Joanna
I think so
Well its a good thing you got out when
you did before she blew up like Vesuvius
The volcano
JOEY Yeah
And speaking of volcanoes man
are they a violent igneousrock formation
What
Oh yeah Lava spewing hot ash
Of course some are dormant
Why are you talking about volcanoes
all of a sudden
Oh we can talk about something else
What do you want to talk about
Vivisection
The vas deferens
The Vietnam War
Oh did anybody see that documentary
on the Korean War
GROUP
Oh yeah
Oh God
Koreas such a beautiful country
With such a sad history
PHOEBE Yeah
Could there be more Kims
JOANNA Whos out there
Its me Good morning
JOANNA
Rachel could you come in here a moment
Yeah sure Um they didnt have
poppyseed bagels
so I have sesame ones Oh my word
I
I seem to have had
a slight office mishap
Could you get the key
off the back of the door
Yeah sure I
Im so sorry
Tell your friend Chandler
that were definitely broken up this time
Okay