Hey remember when I had a monkey
Yeah
PHOEBE Mmhm
Yeah What was I thinking
Hey so whats with the 20 percent tip
Did I do something wrong
Twenty percent is a pretty generous tip
You know whats more generous than that
Fifty percent
You know whats even more generous
I see where youre going
Whats up with the greed Joe
All right look Im sorry you guys
Its just that I gotta get
these new headshots made
and theyre really expensive you know
Im down to like three
Actually two because one of them
I kind of blackened in some teeth
Whyd I do that Ugh
Well isnt there something you can do
to earn a little extra money
I mean cant you pick up
I dont know an extra shift here
Or you know I used to beg for money
Of course it helps if youve got
you know a little of this going on
Wow I still have it Ha ha
JOEY Yeah
Wait dont you have an audition today
Yeah Maybe youll get that job
Oh hahaha
Oh wait a minute
I used to get medical experiments
done on me all the time
Ah finally an explanation
No I used to get paid
for all kinds of medical stuff remember
Lets see Uh
Well I dont wanna donate sperm again
I really prefer doing that at the home office
you know
Ooh ooh maybe they want some
of my blood or spit or something huh
Joey
Yeah
What did I tell you about talking
to your friends while youre working
Uh do it
That guys been waiting for his coffee
for 1 0 minutes
Hes complained about you three times
Now where was I
Hey
Hey what have you been up to
Oh We went to a selfdefense class today
Wow
Yeah Kicking a guy in the crotch
all morning really takes it out of you
Takes it out of you Heh
No now we can kick anybodys ass
Yeah
After one class I dont think so
What you wanna see me
selfdefend myself
Go over there
and pretend youre a sexual predator
Go on I dare you
Of course you can defend yourself
from an attack you know is coming
Thats not enough
Look I studied karate for a long time
And theres a concept
you should really be familiar with
Its what the Japanese call unagi
Isnt that a kind of sushi
No its a concept
Yeah it is it is Its freshwater eel
All right maybe it means that too
Oh I would kill
for a salmonskin roll right now
You know what Fine get attacked
I dont even care
Come on Ross were sorry
Please tell us what it is
Unagi is a state of total awareness
Okay Only by achieving true unagi
can you be prepared
for any danger that may befall you
In case someones trying
to steal your bamboo sleeping mat
or your kettle of fish
All Im saying is
its one thing being prepared
for an attack against like each other
Whole other story being prepared
for an attack I dont know
A surprise
All right you knew that was coming
but that doesnt mean you have unagi
Ooh if we made reservations
we could have unagi in about a halfhour
You know what
Hey hey is Monica here
No
Okay look I need your help
I dont know what to get for Valentines Day
Well Valentines Day was two weeks ago
so I wouldnt get her a calendar
Heh She was working on Valentines Day
so were celebrating it tonight
Oh hey why dont you book a day for both
of you at one of those romantic spas
Ooh Joey
thats actually a really good idea
Yeah and of course crotchless panties
Well as appealing as that does sound
to her boyfriend
and her brother
I cant We promised
wed make each other gifts this year
Oh I love that
You guys
You cant make crotchless panties
You take
You take a pair of scissors and just cut
Okay okay okay
So making things
that sounds so much fun
I thought so too
until I papiermâchéd one of my eyes shut
I love papiermâché What did you make
I made a
What is that
Nothing
Oh
So what are you gonna do
Have you guys made anything
that I could take credit for
Ooh I have I have
I started making these little sock bunnies
Oh for crying out loud
Hey wait a minute That is my sock
Now its your little bunny friend
Okay
This actually is a
Hey
Hey honey
Can I ask you a question
about the Valentines Day gifts
Oh yeah
Do we have to make the entire thing
Yes Why did you forget to make yours
I just have to uh go over to the place
where I made it and pick it up
Okay
I cant wait
Its gonna be the best Valentines Day ever
I cant believe it
Make the presents Make the presents
What
Just so excited to make the presents
Shoot
Hi Im Joey Tribbiani
And with all due respect
Id like to donate some fluids
Were at the end
of one of our research cycles
so were not looking
for applicants now
Thats too bad
Ive kind of been saving up
Uh you sure theres no studies
I can participate in
Well heres a schedule
of whats coming up
Ah thanks
Oh but this one starts now
That one is available now
but only identical twins are eligible
Its a twin study
But its 2000
Sorry
Oh
Well how about this one
Testing the Effects of Joey Tribbiani
on Attractive Nurse Receptionists
We already got the results back
on that one and theyre not good
That was good
Wasnt that a blast
Danger Danger
God Ross
What the hell was that
A lesson in the importance of unagi
Youre a freak
Perhaps
Now Im curious
At what point during those girlish screams
would you have begun to kick my ass
All right so we werent prepared
Im sorry I had to take
such drastic measures to make my point
But look
I just want you guys to be safe
Oh
Danger
Ah huh Unagi
JOEY
Two thousand bucks is a lot of money
Boy I wish I had a twin
Where could I find someone
who looks exactly like me
Hey
Chandler
I sensed it was you
What
Unagi
Im always aware
Okay are you aware that unagi is an eel
Whats up
I cant figure out what to make Monica
Oh Why dont you make her
one of your little jokes
Im going crazy okay
Do you have anything around here
that looks homemade
Oh you know what Shed love this
Its an exact replica of Apollo 8
I made it in the sixth grade
Yeah I guess I could use that I could say
Your love sends me to the moon
Yeah yeah Except Apollo 8
didnt actually land on the moon
But you could write um
Your love lets me orbit the moon twice
and return safely
Wait I cant give this to her
Why not
It says Captain Ross on the side
And it says I hate Monica on the bottom
Oh
PHOEBE  RACHEL Danger
ROSS Aah
Ah Salmonskin roll
Okay okay
Yes honey I made it myself
I cant do it I cant do it
Oh oh A mixed tape A mixed tape
Hey hi
Hey
You ready to exchange gifts
Sure Okay you go first
Okay come here come here
Okay
Okay now its not wrapped
because I just finished it
Okay
But I made you a tape
of what I think are all romantic songs
What a great gift
Oh
Is The Way You Look Tonight on it
Maybe Well have to listen and see
Oh I love it Thank you so much Mwah
Aw Okay Mwah
Okay you ready to open yours
Yeah
Okay
Its a sock bunny
Ha ha Yeah yeah
Remember how I call you bunny
Not really
Well I did one time
And I wanna start doing it more
Thats what this is about
I see
You know um
Phoebe makes sock bunnies
No No she doesnt
Phoebe what she makes thats
Theyre sock rabbits
Theyre completely different Okay okay
Okay I didnt make it Im sorry
I totally forgot about tonight
and that we were supposed
to make the presents
Oh its okay I dont
No no its not okay Its not
I mean youre so incredible
You went through all this time
and effort to make this tape for me
You know Im just gonna
Im gonna make this up to you I will
I am going to cook you anything you want
in here
And Im going to do anything you want
in there
Well I did put a lot of thought
into the tape
Wow
You are way too young to have seen that
Oops Ha ha
Your birthdays in a month and a half
What do you say I forget
to get you a present for that too
You are totally and completely
1 00 percent forgiven.
We have got to wash that
Yeah
Hey do you remember that jacket
that you loved so much
that you thought was too expensive
You have done enough
Ha ha Im gonna wake up early
and get it for you
No you dont have
Get it in black not brown
Oop Your cake is ready
Oop
Its like that old saying
Have sex eat some cake
Hey Mon Hey Chan
Just getting a soda
Who the hell are you
Im Joey
How are you doing
No no no
How you doing
Damn it Carl Go wait in the hall
Look I got to apologize on behalf of Carl
Who the hell is Carl
Oh did I not mention
Carl is a guy I hired to be my identical twin
for a medical research project
You know sometimes the good ideas
are just right in front of you arent they
Look I know it sounds crazy
but I think it might work
But the only problem is Carls acting is
The only problem
Yeah Hes the reason I didnt get
that big Minute Maid commercial
We were supposed to be brothers
but he messed it up
Hey Can I get a little piece of that cake
Pizza We like pizza Get out
Pat Sajak
Yep
Alex Trebek
Oh of course
Chuck Woolery
Definitely
Phoebe you will not find
a single gameshow host
whose ass I cannot kick
Say it
Say we are unagi
Its not something you are
its something you have
Say it
I could easily get out of this
but theres a chance
you could get very very hurt
All right Carl were next
Now remember what is this not gonna be
Another Minute Maid fiasco
Thats right
And what are you not gonna do
Im not gonna talk because
Ah Damn it Carl
Can I have the next one please
Thank you
Joey and Tony Tribbiani
Thats us
But uh this is a study
for identical twins
Thats right Two thousand dollars
But youre not identical twins
Oh my good God
Hey Continuing the countdown
of your favorite meals
Tonight number three
macaroni and cheese
with cutup hot dogs
Look you have done enough okay
You have to stop this now
I will but not tonight
For dinner music I thought we could listen
to that tape that you made me
Oh the mixed tape
Mmhm
When Im awfully low
Oh The Way You Look Tonight
is on here
Dance with me
I will feel a glow
Just thinking of you
And the way you look tonight
You are just the sweetest
you look every night Chandler
Thats why I made you this tape
Happy birthday Love Janice Mwah
No youre the sweetest
Great class Heh
Thanks man
Yeah yeah I was watching
Um hey a couple of questions though
Um you know that last move
where that woman tripped you
and then pinned you to the floor
What would you do next
Well then shed take her keys
and jam them in your
No no no What would you do next
Who me the attacker
Yes thats right
Why
I tried attacking two women
Did not work
What
No I mean its okay
I mean theyre my friends
In fact I was married to one of them
Let me get this straight
You attacked your exwife
Oh no no no Heh
I tried
But I couldnt Thats why Im here
Maybe we could attack them together
Thats a no
I am so so so sorry
Uhhuh
Oh And I will cook anything you want
in here
and do anything you want in there
Yeah you will and are you kidding me
Come on Monica
its our Valentines Day
Please please please
Okay
My funny valentine
Sweet comic valentine
You make me
So are we going in there
I am
Your looks are laughable
ROSS
Aha
Nowhere to run
I dont like sitting up here
Im gonna go over
No Rachel they got here first
Why is Ross doing that
ROSS Danger
Oh my God
Why is he jumping on those women
We should help them
I dont think they need any help