Do you realize were
getting married in four weeks
Four weeks baby Four weeks
You realize you get louder each week
Theres still so much to do
Have you written your vows
I figured Id just buy those
Pat Id like to buy a vow Ha ha
You know Ive no sense of humor
when it comes to this
Right Have you written yours yet
No but I know what Im gonna say
Do you happen to know
what Im gonna say
Lets do it now lt wont be hard
Say whats in your heart
CHANDLER Look at her go
She must love me more than I love her
Whats wrong with me
Ooh dont open that door
Phew Monica there are no words
There are no words
This shouldnt be this hard
Uh Oh Youve done this before
What did you say in your vows
With Carol I promised never
to love another woman until I die
She made no such promise
Im pathetic Monica knows what
to say you should have seen her
RACHEL
Whats the emergency
You have to help me write my vows
All I have is this
I like the pretty drawing
of you in the wedding dress
Thank you
Except your breasts look small
Those are my eyes
Those are my breasts
Oh yeah
Why dont you start
with something simple
Like um
Monica from the moment I met you
I knew I loved you
I cant do that
Everyone this is Chandler
Hi Im Ross little sister
Okay
Okay okay
Um maybe you could start with
Chandler even though
we were friends
there was a part of me
that knew I wanted more
All right theres a nuclear
holocaust Im the last man on Earth
Would you go out with me
Ooh Are we allowed
to lie in the vows
Okay dont talk about those feelings
Just say something about
all the things
hes taught you like
Or all the things you taught him
Everybody knows the erogenous zones
One two three
four five six and seven
There are seven
Thats one
Heh heh Kind of an important one
I was looking at it upside down
Ha You know sometimes that helps
Okay start out with a little one
a two a onetwothree
a three a five
a four a threetwo
two a twofoursix
Twofoursix four two
two fourseven
fiveseven sixseven
seven seven
seven seven seven
seven
Seven
Oh I got it
How about something like
Monica when I look back
over our time together
Yeah
I cant do all of it
Look back over your time together
MONICA
Oh look twins
No fair I dont even have one
how come they get two
Youll get one
Yeah when
All right Ill tell you what
When were 40
if neither of us are married
what do you say we have one
Why wouldnt I be married
Oh no no no
I just meant hypothetically
Hypothetically
why wont I be married
No no
What is it Is there
something unmarriable about me
Uh Uh
Well
Dear God this parachute
is a knapsack
ROSS
Im getting married today
Think he knew I was here
Nice try
MONICA
Wait wait wait
Look Monica
Ah
This is not gonna work
I bet thisll work
You are so great I love you
MONICA
What
I said youre so great
and then I stopped talking
You said you love me
No I didnt
Yes you did
You love me
No I dont
Stop it Stop it
You know I was thinking
what if I uh unpack here
Then all your stuff would be here
Well
What if it was here
Then youd be going back
and forth all the time
Doesnt make any sense
Okay
What if we live together
and you understand what Im saying
We wanted to surprise you
Oh my God
Chandler
in all my life
I never thought Id be so lucky
as to fall in love with my best
My best Theres a reason
why girls dont do this
Okay okay okay Ill do it
I thought
I can do this
that it mattered what I said
or where I said it
Then I realized the only thing
that matters is that you
You make me happier
than I ever thought I could be
And if you let me
Ill spend the rest of my life
trying to make you feel the same way
Monica
Will you marry me
Yes
JOEY Can we come in
Were dying out here
Come in Come in
Were engaged
ALL Yes
JOEY  ROSS Hey
RACHEL Hey
Hi
What have you guys been up to
Uh helping Chandler write his vows
He kicked us out
Joey kept making
inappropriate suggestions
How is Monica I love
your sweet ass inappropriate
Hows Monica doing
Lucky shes got a sweet ass
Shes not so good at writing
In four weeks
theyre gonna be married
Lets just hope it works
Nine out of 1 0 marriages
end in divorce
Heh Thats not true
Youre right Hows the missus
I cant believe
theyre together 3 years
That long
It seems like less
because they hid it from us
JOEY
Hey its me Coming in
Ive had a very long hard day
Uh Im getting chicken Want some
Uh no Bye then
Are you okay
Im so sorry
He wouldnt leave
He kept asking if I wanted chicken
Chicken
I could eat some chicken
Hey Joe
Can I get a uh threepiece
uh coleslaw beans and a Coke
Diet Coke
Why didnt they tell us
I know we were cool about it
You And you
You cannot tell No one knows
How When
It happened in London
In London
We didnt want to make
a big deal out of it
But it is a big deal
I have to tell someone
No no
You cant
Please
We dont want to deal with telling
them Just promise you wont tell
All right
I cant wait to be with you
Ill tell Rachel Im doing laundry
CHANDLER
Laundry huh Is that my new nickname
MONICA
Aw
You know your nickname Mr Big
Oh look theres Monica and Chandler
Hey Hey you guys Hey
Chandler and Monica
Oh my God
Aah Chandler and Monica
Oh my eyes My eyes
Phoebe Phoebe
Its okay Its okay
No Theyre doing it
I know I know
You know
Yes
And Joey but Ross doesnt
so stop screaming
Hey whats going on
What What
Were excited that you
might get this place
Actually it looks really good
It looks pretty good
PHOEBE
Get in here Come on
So they dont know
that Rachel knows
Yes but it doesnt matter
who knows what
Enough of us know
We can just tell them we know
The lying and the secrets
will be over
Or we can not tell them we know
and have a little fun of our own
We better go if were gonna
catch that movie
Bye
RACHEL  CHANDLER Bye
Bye Chandler I miss you already
Did you see
the inappropriate pinching
Actually I did
So now do you believe
that shes attracted to me
Oh my God
My God she knows about us
Phoebe knows about us
I didnt tell them
Them Whos them
Uh Phoebe and Joey
Joey
And Rachel
They made me promise not to tell
They think they are so slick
messing with us
They dont know that we know
that they know
So
Ah yes
The messers become the messees
My God he wants me to come
over and feel his biceps
Are you kidding
No
I cant believe hed do that to Mo
Joey Do they know that we know
No
Joey
They know you know
Ugh I knew it
I cannot believe those two
They thought that they could
mess with us With us
They dont know that we know
they know we know
Joey you cant say anything
Couldnt if I wanted to
This is totally getting out of hand
She wants me to put lotion on her
Shes bluffing
Shes not backing down
She went like this
Hes not backing down
He went to get lotion
Oh man
Arent you guys done yet
The sooner Phoebe breaks Chandler
the sooner this is all over
Ooh I like that
RACHEL Okay
Okay show him your bra
Hes afraid of bras Cant work them
Wow You didnt rip off
any buttons
Its not my first time
You go seduce her until she cracks
Okay give me a second
Did you clean up in here
Of course
Oh youre uh going
Um not without you lover
So this is my bra
Its very very nice
Well come here
Im happy were gonna
have all the sex
You should be Heh Im very bendy
Im gonna kiss you
Not if I kiss you first
Theres nothing left
for us to do but kiss
Here it comes
Our first kiss
Okay okay okay fine you win
Ha
I cant have sex
Why not
Im in love with Monica
Youre what
Love her Thats right I love her
I love her
I love you Monica
I love you too Chandler
I thought you guys were doing it
I didnt know you were in love
Thats it its over
Everybody knows
Well Ross doesnt
Wed like it if no one told him yet
No
What are you doing
Get off my sister
Friends getting married
its gotta change things
Think itll be different
How can it not be
Theyre gonna have kids
and hang out with other couples
who have kids
And maybe theyll leave the city
to be near a Volvo dealership
Things change
I dont want them
to move to a Volvo dealership
Itll be okay Joe Heh
Sorry I just
I like things the way they are
Whos this little naked guy
Uh that naked guy would be me
Ha aw look at the little thing
Hahaha
Yes
Yes fine that is my penis
Can we be grownups now
Who are those people
Got me
Oh thats Nana right there
Wow
Lets see
Me and the gang at Java Joes
Wow Monica you look like
your grandma How old was she
Lets see 1 939
Yeah uh 24 25
Huh Looks like a fun gang
Ooh Look look look
I got Monica naked
RACHEL
Let me see
No that would be me again
Hey you guys
PHOEBE Hey
JOEY Hey
CHANDLER Whats going on
Well we were just talking about
you guys getting married
and how great it is
Yeah you can get a Volvo
If thats what you really want
Thats so sweet
Hmm
So we both finished our vows
Can we read them
As long as I dont hear his
and he doesnt hear mine
RACHEL Okay
PHOEBE Okay
Aw
Oh
Oh thats beautiful
Funny one Good
Will you marry me
Hahaha
What I dont get it
Oh yeah
Man this is hilarious
Chandler
Dont worry well make yours funnier
Okay what do you think
Dude
I have never known love like this
You really like it
Dude
How did you write this
I stole Monicas
and changed the name Shh
You cant do that
If he goes first he can