Joey would you slow down
Theyre not gonna be sold out of papers
at 100 in the morning
Im excited
Ive never gotten reviewed before
You were so amazing as the king
Im really impressed I was
But you know what
You might wanna consider
wearing underwear next time
Because when you sat on your throne
you could kind of see your
royal subjects
Here it is Here it is
The only thing worse than
the mindless adolescent direction
was Joseph Tribbianis disturbingly
unskilled portrayal of the king
Okay look
That is one guys opinion
All right Pheebs read yours
Okay
The only thing worse than the mindless
adolescent direction
Does anybody have one
from a different paper
Ross read yours
I dont want to
Joey honey they dont know
what theyre talking about
Maybe they do
Ive been doing this 10 years
and I havent gotten anywhere
Theres gotta be a reason
Come on man youre just uh
paying your dues
No no no Its too hard
Its not worth it I quit
What
Thats crazy
Wait wait one minute Wait a minute
I believe this will change your mind
In a mediocre play Joseph Tribbiani was
able to achieve brilliant new levels of
Continued on page 153
sucking
When I was little
I wanted to be a veterinarian
But then I found out you have to
put your hands into cows and stuff
Hi
Are you okay
Yeah just a tough day at work
you know
Stegosaurus fell over trapped a kid
I know this jacket
This is Fun Bobbys jacket
Where is he What Hes here isnt he
Maybe
Dont toy with me
Geller
Hey Fun Bobby
Whoa hey You been working out
Not at all
I love this guy
I was so psyched to hear
youre back with my sister
You and me both
So whatd I miss Come on
Oh We were trying
to make Joey feel better
Hey do you need me to pick you up
No Im all right man really
No Im picking you up
Hey no seriously
I dont need you to
All right it still works
Okay
Now before I go does anybody else
need to be picked up
Im still gonna go
Okay Ill see you later babe
Ah
Public display of affection coming up
You can avert your eyes
Mm
See you
Bye
Fun Bobby is so great
Oh isnt he
I really think this time it may work with him
I mean he makes me feel so good
And Ive been feeling so lousy
you know no job no boyfriend
Well at least my cup is half full
Half full of love
And for our twoweek anniversary
hes gonna take me to his cousins cabin
Cabin of love
We went through a lot of wine tonight
you guys
Really I only had two glasses
I just had a glass
Two
I had one glass
I had about a mug full in this lovely
I got boned at the Museum
of Natural History mug
Okay so thats what Two bottles
And yet somehow we went through five
Whoa
Oh
So what So he drank a lot tonight
Yeah but you know
now that I think about it
I dont think Ive ever seen Fun Bobby
without a drink in his hand
Yeah Ooh ooh yeah you know
Did you notice how he always
starts his stories with um
Okay I was so wasted or
Oh we were so bombed
Or um So I wake up and Im
in this Dumpster in Connecticut
Monica have you ever been with him
when he wasnt drinking
Well we just happen to go to
a lot of places where you might drink
I mean how do you go to a winetasting
without having a drink
Or to a club or to the
zoo
Rach does this have nonfat milk
Um I dont know why dont you taste it
Mm No
Oh well too late you already had some
What do you say we make these uh
coffees Irish
Um cake
Yeah were gonna
Were gonna get some cake
You know it seems like youve been
making an awful lot of stuff Irish lately
I would make them Belgian but the waffles
are hard to get into that flask
Bobby
Yeah okay
Look maybe this is none of my business
or maybe it is I dont know
But um Im kind of worried about you
Okay look this isnt the first time
somebody said something to me about this
But I dont know I always made excuses
like Im just a social drinker
Or Hey come on its Flag Day
So what are you saying now
I guess Im saying
Ill try and quit
I kind of like that you worry about me
So whats going on
I am gonna try and quit drinking
Oh Why
Hey
Guess whos back in show business
Ooh ooh Lorne Greene
No Pheebs You know why
Because hes dead
Oh no
Okay I guess this is gonna seem
bittersweet now
but Joey thats who
Oh yay
Really
My agent just called me with an audition
for Days of our Lives
Kick ass
We have to celebrate
We should do a soap opera theme
Hey yeah We could all sleep together
and then one of us could get amnesia
Rach what time do you get off
Were all gonna do something tonight
Uh well actually Im already done
Ahem But I kind of got plans
You have other friends
Yeah I uh I have a date
What
With a man
What What is so strange
about me having a date
What about Ross
Are you still mad at him
because he made that list about
No no Im not mad at him
Im not really anything at him anymore
What are you talking about
I dont know
Whatever I was feeling Im not
But you guys came so close
Oh I know Im sorry you guys
Youre gonna have to get used to the fact
that I will not be dating Ross
Here he is Hi
Guys this is Russ
Hi
No no no Im not saying
youre not talented Youre very talented
Its just that with the bird dead and all
theres very little act left
Oh honey give me a break will you
Oh oh Ill talk to you later
Well theres my favorite client
So tell me darling
how was the audition
Well I think it went pretty well
I got a callback for Thursday
Joey Have you ever seen me ecstatic
No
Well here it is
Okay Uh listen theres something
I want to talk to you about
The network casting lady
Oh isnt Lori a doll
Yeah yeah shes great
But I kind of got the feeling
that she was sort of coming on to me
And I definitely would get the part
if I were to you know
if I would have sent the little general in
Oh
I see Well Im just gonna
put in a call here
and well find out whats going on
and straighten it out
Yeah hi Lori please
Hi darling
So how about Joey Tribbiani
for the part of the cab driver
Isnt he terrific
Uhhuh
Okay doll talk to you later
Yeah youre gonna have to
sleep with her
Whats the matter
Fun Bobby
What Isnt he sober
Oh hes sober all right
Just turns out that Fun Bobby
was fun for a reason
Ah Okay
All right here you go sweetie
Thanks You wanna hear something funny
Oh God yes
There are no hardware stores open
past midnight in the Village
That is funny
I needed to buy a hammer
the other night
and Im out walking
around the neighborhood
But apparently
there are no hardware stores open
past midnight in the Village
Uh say honey dont you have to
be at your interview
Oh yeah
See you guys
Bye
ridiculously dull Bobby
Oh my God
Hes not that bad
Not that bad
Did you not hear the hammer story
Okay okay dont get all squinky
Maybe it was just the kind of story
where you had to be there
But Im gonna be there
For the rest of my life
I cant break up with him
I made him quit drinking
Hes dull because of me
All right dont say that
Hes probably always been dull
You just you know
set it free
Hi
Hey Ross Ah
Hi Russ
Ive just got two more tables to clean
and then well go okay
Okay Ill just sit here and uh
chat with your uh
friendtype people
Rachel Um hi
Hi
Okay
So you know what youre doing right
Ha ha Waitressing
Well yeah But no I mean um
Doesnt Russ just
remind you of someone
Huh Bob Saget
Oh yeah
No no no Oh oh
Hi
Oh my oh
What Whats wrong
I Okay
Shes just upset because she uh
She buttered a spider
into her toast this morning
Mmhm
All right
Listen Pheebs
This is gonna be okay
Ross Russ Russ Ross
Hi
Are you a uh friend of Rachels
Yes Yes I am
Actually Im uh kind of a
you know
a datetype thing
of Rachels
A date
Yeah Im her date
Oh Oh youre uh
Oh youre the date
You know this is actually good
because if we ever lose Ross
we have a spare
Oh You are the uh paleontologist
Yes Yes I am And you are a
Periodontist
See Now theyre
as different as night and
later that night
Well I am going to uh get a beverage
Heh
Uh it was nice uh meeting you
Ditto
I uh Well I met Russ
Oh
Hey I didnt know
we were uh seeing other people
Well were not seeing each other so
Huh
Well uh for your information
theres a woman at the museum
whos curator of moths and other uh
winged things
whos uh let it be known
that she is drawn to me much like a
you know Ahem
Well so far Ive been keeping her at bay
but uh if this is the deal
Yeah this is the deal
Okay well um have a nice evening
Thank you
Russ are you ready
Yeah
Bye
Shes dating
Yes Yes but did you see
who she was dating
What do you mean
Do you not see it
See what
I dont know what she sees
in that goober
It takes him what
Like I dont know uh
hello a week to get out a sentence
Yeah its annoying isnt it
Yeah
Hey
Whoa whoa
Im guessing you didnt get the part
or uh Italy called
and said it was hungry
Well the parts mine if I want it
Oh my God
Yeah If Im willing to sleep
with the casting lady
Oh my
God
Ten years Ive been waiting for
a break like this Chandler Ten years
I mean Days of our Lives
Thats actually on television
So what are you gonna do
I guess I could sleep with her
I mean
How can I do that
Well Ive got a popup book
that told me everything I needed to know
Ive never slept with someone for a part
Well is she
Sorry
Is she goodlooking
Yeah
Shes totally goodlooking
I mean if I met her in a bar or something
Id be buying her breakfast
You know after having slept with her
You know maybe this isnt
such a big deal
I mean the way that I see it is you get
a great job and you get to have sex
You know Throw in a tree and a fat guy
and youve got Christmas
I just I just dont think
that I want it that way though you know
I mean lets say I do make it all right
Im always gonna look back and wonder
if it was because of my talent
or because of you know
the little general
Didnt you used to call it the little major
Yeah but after Denise DeMarco
I had to promote it
Can I get you something from the bar
Yes I would like something
No No thank you
No if you want a drink its okay with me
Ive gotta get used to it
No no really
I wouldnt feel right about it
Just some water please
So the light went out in my refrigerator
Scotch on the rocks with a twist
Im sorry
Hey were having some fun now
huh Ross
Wanna do another one
Huh Russ
Okay Eleven letters
atomic element number 101
ends in ium
Dysprosium
Ha ha Dysprosium
Try mendelevium
And weenie number two has it
Unless of course 9 Down Nights in White
Satin was sung by the Doody Blues
You dont see it
You actually dont see it
What
Okay honey youre dating Ross
No Pheebs Im dating Russ
Russ is Ross Russ Ross
Steve sleeve
Okay no one is named sleeve
Phoebe what the hell
are we talking about
Other than their names being similar
Im sorry I do not see what youre seeing
For your information
its a card sharp not a card shark
You could not be more wrong
You could try
but you would not be successful
Okay Im gonna get some more coffee
before the pinching and eyepoking begins
I know what your problem is
Oh you do do you
Mmhm Youre jealous
Uh of what
Youre jealous because Im a real doctor
Hey youre a doctor of gums
Thats the smallest body part
you can major in
Its like day one floss
Day two heres your diploma
Now you listen
No no
Let me finish
No let me finish
No you let me fin
Hi
Ew
Ew ew ew
Did Joey say what he was gonna do
No
I dont even think he knew
Hey would you sleep with somebody
to get a great job
I dont know
Who would I have to sleep with
Me
Why would I have to sleep with you
Its my game You want the job or not
Hi
Hey
Good morning
Where you going
Bobby and I are going away
for the weekend Remember
Oh
Whats with all the bottles of liquor
Whats going on
Is uh Bobby drinking again
Oh no this is not for him
This is for me
That way hes still sober but I find
his stories about shoelaces more amusing
Ugh God Even his knock is boring
Hi Ill be ready in just a second
Uh could I talk to you a minute
Sure
This is really hard for me to say
Oh God You fell off the wagon
Oh no no
Its about you
What about me
I think you may have a drinking problem
What these
No these are um for cuts and scrapes
Look I am just not strong enough to be
in a codependent relationship right now
Oh shoot
Well anyway
I hope we can be friends
Okay
Take care
Okay You too
Bye
What happened
Well we kind of broke up
Aw
Does anybody want these
Ill take one
Sometimes I like to hold stuff like this
and pretend Im a giant
Hey
Hey Howd the callback go
Ugh it was unbelievable
I walked in there and she was all over me
So what did you do
Well I couldnt do it
I told her I didnt want the part that way
Good for you
Oh wait wait wait
But then after I left her office
she caught up with me at the elevator
and offered me an even bigger part
So and
So you are now looking
at Dr Drake Ramoray neurosurgeon
recurring in at least four episodes
All right
All right I gotta go shower
Hi
Oh hey
I guess you guys heard
Rachel dumped me
Yeah Im sorry man
All she said was that I remind her
too much of somebody
You have any idea who
shes talking about
Oh I do Its Bob Saget
She hates him
Oh
Hey
Hey Julie
Hey how are you doing
Oh I dont know I mean
its definitely weird not being with Ross
but I guess Im doing okay
Actually Ive got some of his stuff
that he um