So honey this uh
This threesome thing Uh heh
How are we even gonna find
Actually Im making a list of women
I know who might be into this
Oh Wow
Huh
Boy
Well someones been
doing their homework
Yeah Oh and I know Gail Rosten
is in there twice
but she is so
Oh I know Ha ha
You know just talking about it
is getting me kind of
I know Me too
Yeah
I think Bens asleep
Oh um
You know I think itll be
better if we just save it
Yeah Heh
Right Save it I can do that
Hey Pheebs
PHOEBE Hey
Hows it going
Ive got to get out of this bed
Im going crazy here Crazy
Here you go sweetie
What the hell is this herbal tea
I hate herbal tea
I put some honey in it
Nyeh nyeh honey nyeh nyeh
She doesnt know she was fired
No the doctors say it may kill her
What are you two girls
whispering about over there
But I think we should tell her
Ugh I mean its just so realistic
I know Yeah
His names Pat
Pat the dog
Oh Oh I get it Ha ha
Oh God
You uh You
ready for a refill
Oh I probably shouldnt
Oh
So I will Ha
Wow
Its like its raining
Pretty cool huh
But if you think a fish wouldnt get
sucked into the mechanism
well youd be wrong
Um can I use your bathroom
Its uh right through there
Okay Ah
You know I gotta tell you
If someone told me a week ago
that I would be peeing
in Joey Tribbianis apartment
Lifes pretty great isnt it
I hope youre hungry
Were starting with oysters
You know what they say about oysters
dont you
They have parasites
No Ha ha
Um well some people say
that oysters are an aphrodisiac
What people
People
People say it
Come here
So oysters huh
Hahaha
And then were gonna have a little
Middle Eastern couscous
Something we can eat
with our hands
When we were studying
communicable diseases
No no no
Its sensual
Oh Didnt know Okay
Okay
Oh no
Im sorry its the hospital
The food looks great
Save me some
I cant promise anything
Were really gonna do this huh
Looks like it
If this is too weird for you
you can still back out
I got it
Okay
Susan hi
Hey
Thank you so much for coming
I wouldnt have missed it for the world
Im Ross by the way
Hello Ross
I love what youve done with this space
Thank you so much Heh
How hot is this
Im sorry youre here with me
instead of Roger
Yeah me too
Well I could make it seem
like hes here
Heres some littleknown facts
about couscous
They didnt add the second cous
until 1 979
Stop it Thats not funny
Okay
Im sorry okay Its just
tonight was supposed to be
you know a big deal
What was tonight
You dont want to know what tonight was
Okay
What was tonight
Tonight was going to be my first time
With Roger
Not just with Roger Oh my God
All right relax
Mr IveHadSexFourTimes
Four different women
Ive had sex way more times
How many
Nine
Im just waiting for the perfect guy
Well good Good for you
You really think Rogers the perfect guy
No but hes not a horrible guy
Thats what I tell girls about me
Chandler Im gonna die a virgin
No youre not
You are sweet and wonderful
and this is gonna happen for you
Oh really When
Do you want to do it with me
Okay
I was kidding
So was I
Youre such an amazing actor
How do you know where
Dr Drake Ramoray leaves off
and Joey Tribbiani begins
Well with Dr Drake
they always tell me what to say
And with Joey I pretty much have to
make it up on my own
Wow
Mm
Tell me something Whoa
I just fell right off the couch there
Yeah you did
Im okay
Here you go Let me ask you a question
Whoops Yeah
When was the last time
someone told you
just how beautiful you are
Wow
I cant feel my hands
Come on Come here
Huh
Oh
Ooh
We cant do this
No
Oyster
Yeah
If If If we did do this
thered be a lot of pressure on me
Because youve waited a long time
and I wouldnt want to disappoint you
But I have nothing to compare it to
So even if you were horrible
how would I know
I do like that
Its harder for me
I have four women to compete with
Well if it helps there were only three
So itd just be for tonight
Absolutely lt would just be one
friend helping out another friend
Stop it Were not doing this
Lets do it
No
Okay
So um
Do you have any uh moves
I have some moves
I have no moves
Okay
Oh okay what you doing there
Im sorry this is just too weird
Yeah forget it
What if I turn out the lights
Okay
CHANDLER
Oh yeah
MONICA Chandler
CHANDLER Yeah
MONICA
Thats the couch
Oh my God
I know
Ill tell you something
We are gonna do that again
Oh okay
Ah
Morning
Oh right
Yeah
Oh God
Oh I cant believe Joey Tribbiani
heard me throw up
He actually saw you a little bit too
No
Oh God we We didnt uh
No No no
Not after seeing that
God Im just a horrible person
Well why
Because Im married
Thats right Im a married woman
I came to a TV stars apartment
to have an affair Ugh
Thats ridiculous
Im not a star
Im just a regular famous actor
And Im a horrible horrible person
Rachel will you stop saying that
Hey Hey look
Remember on the show
when Capri was dying
And she gave me
The ring from the cave Yeah
Uh
Oh my God
They let you keep that stuff
Sure As long as they dont find out
you can keep whatever you want
And I want you to have it
No I couldnt
Yes Yes
And every time you look at it
I want you to remember
that you are a good person
Now you had the chance to cheat
and with me
But you didnt
And thats what this ring stands for
But I thought that ring stood for
Capris undying love for her brother
Look you want the ring or not
Yeah
ROSS
Hey look at you Youre up
JOEY All right
I thought Id try to take a walk
You pour me some water
Ill be back soon
Whoa whoa
Youre not gonna call work are you
No Ive learned my lesson
Lets go Come on Move it
Phoebe come on
Shoes briefcase Thanks Lou
Good luck with the gallbladder
Hey Joe
did you ever have a threesome
Look Ross Carols great and Im sure
youre a very attractive man but
No I
No The reason Im asking is that
I sort of had one last night
You
Yeah
Wow All right
So Was it amazing
It was heh
okay
Just okay Did you do it right
Look its just did you ever
go to a party and think
Would anyone really miss me
if I werent here
Huh
But still Ross
Your worst day with two women
pretty much better than any other day
Oh oh no absolutely
Yeah
Its just
my part seemed to be over
pretty quickly
and then there was
a lot of waiting around
Oh
But you got to be with
both of them right
Not really
Eh just Carol
Not the other one
No she kept kicking me away
You dont want that
No
Hey at least you got to see a lot of stuff
Oh I saw a lot of stuff
You get a little bored
A little
Yeah Made a snack
Yeah
Whatd you have
Just a sandwich
Turkey A little mustard
Sounds good
It really was
Hey
Let me tell you about this chick
I scored with last night
Oh no wait a minute that was you
Heh
Hey check me out Im a slut
So you uh
want to do something tonight
Oh I cant
Dr Rogers coming over again
Oh Oh right
I remember a time
Are you okay
Yeah totally
Totally Are you
Great Its so amazing
Last time Dr Roger came over
I was so nervous
But after being with you
Im like Can the doctor see me now
Ill bet he can
I dont have an appointment
but I sure could use a physical Ha ha
You sure youre okay
Dont worry about me Ill be fine
Aah
My God Barry
You said youd be away all weekend
Oh
Thats right Im sorry I am early
Finish please
Surprise look whos back
Hey Pheebs
Hey
Call security
Pheebs uh didnt you get fired
Heh I dont think so
Phoebe
Jack Hey Ha ha
What are you doing here
All better Back to work
This clown from research
told me I was fired
He should do his research huh
Hahaha
Well you were fired
Nuhuh
I told that guy
who answered your phone
Oh okay I didnt get that message
So this doesnt count
Anyway Ill be in my office
Ah heh
Phoebe you dont have an office
All right Ill work right here
This is good Next to this plant
Phoebe lets
Youre in my office
Look Ive made a lot of cash for this
company I am talking big bucks
Pesos Yen Rubles
You make one little mistake
You lost 1 3 million dollars
So now this is all about money
You know its bad enough that
Ow
Oh you have got to be kidding
Are you all right
Im having another heart attack
What
Call 91 1
Dumbass
Pheebs hows it going
They fired me
and Im having a heart attack
Well welcome back
Yeah
Hi Ross
Hi Rachel
Is Joey Tribbiani here
Um no
If you see him please tell him
that Im looking for him
and that this time
I am not gonna throw up
Are you okay
Me Im great
Im fine Im so good
But you know whos not great
Men
Youre a man right Ross
Yeah
Sit down
Okay
Let me uh ask you something
Do wedding vows mean squat
to you people
Why is it that the second
we go out of town
bam there you are in bed
with the neighbors dogwalker
Were sorry
No seriously Seriously What has
happened to the sanctity of marriage
Didnt you spend last night at Joeys
Oh what are you a detective
I dont know whats going on
with you and your husband
and what is hopefully
an adult dogwalker
Look can I just say
not all men are like that
Ugh
Hey there are some men
wholl do whatever
to make their marriage work
There are some men
who will stand by and watch
as their wives engage in what can
only be described as a twosome
with some woman she barely knows
from the gym
Who are these men
Just men A guy I know
Well you might want to tell him
it sounds like his wife
is gay
She is not
Shes gay
Oh my God
She is so gay
I cant believe this
Good day for married people huh
Im sorry your husband cheated on you
Im sorry your wife is gay
I guess women arent that great either
Try telling my wife that
Okay to come in
Yeah come in eat whatever you want
Dr Roger got beeped again
Yeah I know Guess who beeped him
What
Im the ruptured spleen Ha ha
Why would you do that
Because you shouldnt be with him
You should be with me
Really
When you were talking about Roger
that was killing me Look
Things like last night dont just happen
At least not to me I mean
with the other two women
in the morning I couldnt wait
to just go hang out with my friends
But with you
heh I was you know
already with a friend
Chandler
You probably dont want to go out with me
I make too many jokes
Ive never been in a serious relationship
There was just one woman
wasnt there
No there were two
Including me
Oh yeah
To finally make you see
One of them wont do it
But the second will set you free
Tell all your hate and anger
Its time to say goodbye
And that is just what I will do
Soon as those bastards I worked for die
La lala la la la la la la la
La la la la la lalala la