Heres little Ben nodding off
Aww look at Aunt Monicas little boy
Look hes got Ross haircut
Oh let me see
Oh God
Is he just the sweetest thing
You must just want
to kiss him all over
That would be nice
Pfft
Pardon
Nothing Just a little extra air
in my mouth Pfft
Hey Chan can you help me out here
I promise Ill pay you back
Oh yeah right
Including the waffles last week
you now owe me
17 jillion dollars
I will really
Ill pay you back this time
Wheres the money coming from
Im helping out at the NYU
Med School with some uh research
What kind of research
Uh just you know science
Science
Yeah I think Ive heard of that
Its a fertility study
Joey
Please tell me youre only
donating your time
Come on you guys
Its not that big a deal
I just go down there
every other day
and make my contribution
to the project
Hey but at the end of two weeks
I get 700
Wow youre gonna be making money
hand over fist
Okay we got the coleslaw
We got the buns
Weve got the groundup flesh
of formally cute cows and turkeys
Men are here
We make fire
Cook meat
Then put out fire by peeing
no get invited back
Cute cute
Oh Melanie called Shes gonna be late
Oh okay
So how are things going with you two
Is she becoming your special someone
I dont know Shes uh
Shes pretty great
Yeah What does she think of
your little science project
You think Im gonna tell a girl I like
that Im also seeing a cup
The mans got a point
Well the tough thing is
she really wants to have sex with me
Crazy bitch
I still got a week left in the program
and according to the rules
if I want to get the money Im not allowed
to conduct any personal experiments
if you know what I mean
Joey we always know what you mean
Hey
How long did you think
this barbecue was gonna last
Im going to China
Jeez you say one thing and eh
Youre going to China
Its uh for the museum
Someone found a bone
We want the bone
they dont want us to have it
So Im going to try to persuade them
Its a whole big bone thing
Anyway Im gonna be gone
for like a week
So uh if you wanna reach me
you cant So heres my itinerary
Um
Heres a picture of me
Oh let me see
Could you take it to Carols now and then
and show it to Ben so he doesnt forget me
Yeah
Hi Ben
Im your father
I am The Head Pahh
This barbecues gonna be very fun
Is Rachel here Um I wanted to wish her
a happy birthday before I left
Oh no shes out having drinks with Carl
Oh Heh
Hey whos Carl
The guy she met at the coffeehouse
No
See theres this guy she met at
The coffeehouse Right
So you do know who he is Heh
Im gonna go say goodbye
to the guys
Hey you know what
Tell them that bone story
Hi
Hey
I have to go to China
The country
No this big pile of dishes
in my Moms breakfront
Do you guys know who Carl is
Lets see Alvin Simon Theodore
No
Well Rachels having drinks with him
Oh no
How can she when shes never
shown interest in you
Forget about her
Hes right man Please move on
Go to China Eat Chinese food
Of course there they just call it food
Yeah I guess I dont know
All right just give her this
for me okay
Listen were just looking out for you
I know
We want you to be happy
And I may only have a couple beers
in me but I love you man
Im still on my first
I just think youre nice
Anyway thats when me and my friends
started this fruitbasket business
We call ourselves
The Three Basketeers Ha ha
Like The Three Musketeers
only with fruit
Oh
Okay
How do you like your burgers
No Presents first food later
Hold on there tiger
Hows it going
How you holding up
Well not so good
She thinks tonights the night
were gonna complete the transaction
if you know what I
And you do Heh
So uh have you ever thought about
being there for her
What do you mean
You know just be there for her
Not following you
Think about it
Okay Im guessing this is from
Well thank you Melanie
Okay this one right here is from me
Okay
Hmm Ah its light
It rattles Its
Travel Scrabble
Ha ha hey
Wow Thank you
This ones from Joey
It feels like a book I think its a book
Feels like a book And its a book
Its Dr Seuss
That book got me through
some tough times
There is a little child
inside this man
The doctors say if they remove it
hell die
Whos this from
Thats uh Ross
Ah
Oh my God
He remembered
Remembered what
It was like months ago
We were walking by this antique store
and I saw this pin in the window
I told him it was just like one
my grandmother had when I was little
Aw I cant believe he remembered
Well sure but can you
play it on a plane
Oh its so pretty
This mustve cost him a fortune
I cant believe he did this
Ross Remember when he
fell in love with Carol
and bought her that ridiculously
expensive crystal duck
What did you just say
Crystal duck
No no no
The um The love part
Oh my God
Oh no no no no
Thats good
Just keep rubbing your head
Thatll turn back time
This is unbelievable
I mean this is unbelievable
I know This is really really huge
No its not Its small
its tiny its petite its wee
Uhuh I dont think any of our lives
will ever be the same ever again
Is there a mute button on this woman
I think this is so great
I mean you and Ross
Did you have any idea
No none
My first night in the city
he mentioned asking me out
but nothing ever happened
so I just
What else did he say
Does he want to go out with me
Given that hes desperately
in love with you
he wouldnt mind getting
a cup of coffee or something
Ross
All this time
Ive gotta talk to him
Hes in China
The country
Wait his flight doesnt leave
for 45 minutes
What about the time difference
From here to the airport
Yes
Youre never gonna make it
Ive got to try
What are you gonna say to him
I dont know
Maybe you shouldnt go
Right because if youre gonna
break his heart that can wait
Yeah but if its good news tell him now
Maybe Ill know when I see him
Here look All right does this help
No
All I know is I cannot wait a week
This is just too big
Ive just got to talk to him Ive got
Ill see you later
I love you
Deal with me first
All right
Ross Ross
Excuse me pardon me
Hi Your boarding pass
Hi
No I need to talk to my friend
Sorry youre not allowed on the jetway
unless you have a boarding pass
He just went on Hes right there
in the blue jacket Can I just
Im sorry Federal regulations
All right um then could you please
just give him a message for me
Please This is very important
All right Whats the message
Uh I dont know
Excuse me Sir
I have a message for you
What
Its from Rachel She loved the present
Shell see you when you get back
What
Toby I dont know
what shes talking about
Theres no Rachel
Dont give me that deep freeze
Oh Joey Joey Joey
I think I blacked out there
for a minute
It was nothing
Well now we gotta
find something fun for you
Ahh you know what
Forget about me Lets uh
Lets give you another turn
Me again
Sure Why not
Boy Somebodys gonna get
a big fruit basket tomorrow
I gotta tell you you are nothing like
I thought you would be
How do you mean
I just had you pegged as one of those
guys who are always Me me me
Ha ha
But you
youre a giver
Youre like the most generous
man I ever met
I mean youre practically a woman
So uh Rach do you want to save
this wrapping paper
Its only a little torn
Are you gonna go for it with Ross
or should I throw it out
I dont know
Thought about it
all of the way there
and I thought about it
all the way back and uh
You know its Ross
You know what I mean Its Ross
Sure
I dont know This is just
my initial gut feeling
but Im thinking
itd be really great
Oh my God me too
Oh wed be like friendsinlaw
The best part is you already
know everything about him
Its like starting on the 15th date
But it would be like
starting on the 15th date
Another good point
No I mean
At the 15th date youre already
in a relationshipy place
Youre committed
Huh
What happens if it doesnt work out
Why isnt it working out
I dont know sometimes it doesnt
Is he not cute enough for you
Does he not make enough money
No Im just
Maybe theres someone else
Is there Is there someone else
No there is no one else
Then why the hell
are you dumping my brother
Wha
Hey big
Shh
Spender
Shes still asleep
So howd it go
It was amazing
You know how you think
youre great in bed
The fact youd even ask
shows how little you know me
Well its like
last night I couldnt do the thing
that usually makes me great
So I had to do all this other stuff
And the response I got Man oh man
It was like a tickertape parade
Yes I know As it happens my room
is very close to the parade route
It was amazing and not just for her
Uhuh For me too
Its like all of a sudden Im blind
but all my other senses
are heightened
You know Its like
I was able to appreciate it
on another level
I didnt know you had another level
I know Neither did I
Hey great skirts Birthday present
Yeah
From who
From you
I exchanged the blouse you got me
Well its the thought
Doesnt Ross flight get in
in a couple hours
At gate 27B
Uh yeah
Monica you know
Ive been thinking about it
Ive decided this Ross thing
is not a good idea
Why
Because I feel
like I wouldnt
just be going out with him
I would be going out with all of you
Ugh thered be all this pressure and
No pressure no pressure
Nothing has even happened yet
and youre already so
Im not so
I was a teensy bit weird at first
but Ill be good I promise
Who is it
Its me Carl
Come on up
Behind my brothers back
Is the kind of crazy thing
you wont be hearing from me
Seven hundred bucks
All right you did it
Do we have any fruit
Man hell of a two weeks huh
You know what though
I really feel I learned something
So youll stick with this
its all for her thing
What are you crazy
When a blind man gets his sight back
does he walk around like this
Im just saying if I see one more
picture of Ed Begley Jr
in that stupid electric car
Im gonna shoot myself
Dont get me wrong Im not against
environmental issues per se
its just that guy
I cant believe youd rather
go out with him than me
Excuse me please
Im trying to have a date here
Fine just stop thinking about me
Cant do it can you
So Im thinking about you
So what
I dont get it What do you see
in this guy anyway
Well he seems to be
a very nice guy
I mean come on buddy
Get a real car
Rachel come on Give us a chance
Ross its too hard
No no
Because itll get weird
for everyone else
Who cares about them This is about us
Ive been in love with you
since the ninth grade
Youre like my best friend
I know
If we broke up and I lost you
Whoa
Why do you think well break up
Have you been involved with someone
where you havent broken up
No
But it only has to happen once
You and I know
we are perfect for each other
Right
So the only question is
Are you attracted to me
I dont know
I mean Ive never looked at you
that way before
Well start looking
Wow
Exactly
And you just know
Im gonna be the guy
caught behind this hammerhead
in traffic
Right
Heh
Youre right
You know what
What
I forgot Im supposed to pick up
a friend at the airport
I am so sorry Im so
If you want to stay
and finish your drinks please do
Im sorry I gotta go Im sorry
But
Excuse me Pardon me Excuse me
Im sorry Ha ha
Toby for Gods sake will you let it go
Theres no Rachel
Oh hey I got that
Oh
Thanks sweetie
No problem
I cannot wait
for you to meet my friends
Really You dont think
theyll judge and ridicule me
No they will I just uh
Cant wait Heh
Cant wait
Come on theyre gonna love you